<FTL>
<!--Player flagship surges-->
<event name="FLAGSHIP_STAGE2_TRACKER">
	<clearSuperDrones player="true"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="POWER_SURGE_DRONES" seeded="false" loops="999999999" thisFight="true" minTime="20.0" maxTime="30.0">
		<warningMessage id="warning_power_surge_player" x="444" y="46" time="5.0" r="120" g="255" b="120" centerText="true" flash="true" sound="surgeWarning" useWarningLine="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</event>
<event name="POWER_SURGE_DRONES">
	<superDrones player="true"/>
</event>

<event name="FLAGSHIP_STAGE3_TRACKER">
	<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE1</removeItem>
	<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE2</removeItem>
	<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE3</removeItem>
	<clearSuperDrones player="true"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="FLAGSHIP_POWER_SURGE_3" seeded="false" loops="999999999" thisFight="true" minTime="20.0" maxTime="30.0">
		<warningMessage id="warning_power_surge_player" x="444" y="46" time="5.0" r="120" g="255" b="120" centerText="true" flash="true" sound="surgeWarning" useWarningLine="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</event>
<event name="FLAGSHIP_POWER_SURGE_3">
	<loadEventList seeded="false">
		<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE1" req="MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE1" lvl="0"/>
		<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE2" req="MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE1"/>
		<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE3" req="MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE2"/>
		<event name="POWER_SURGE_SHIELD" req="MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE3"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event>
<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE1">
	<hiddenAug>MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE1</hiddenAug>
	<superBarrage player="true"/>
</event>
<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE2">
	<hiddenAug>MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE2</hiddenAug>
	<superBarrage player="true"/>
</event>
<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE3">
	<hiddenAug>MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE3</hiddenAug>
	<superBarrage player="true"/>
</event>
<event name="POWER_SURGE_SHIELD">
	<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE1</removeItem>
	<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE2</removeItem>
	<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_STAGE3_SURGE3</removeItem>
	<superShields player="true"/>
</event>


<!--Butt Buddies quest-->
<ship name="SHIP_SLUG_BUTT_BUDDIES" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_HACKER">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The Slug ship has been destroyed. You scrap the remains.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>계속...</text>
			<event load="BUTT_BUDDIES_REVENGE"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>The Slug ship has been dealt with. You scrap the remains.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>계속...</text>
			<event load="BUTT_BUDDIES_REVENGE"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<event name="BUTT_BUDDIES">
	<quest>
		<nebulaBeacon>true</nebulaBeacon>
		<createNebula>true</createNebula>
	</quest>
	<text>The coordinates are surprisingly accuracte, leading you right into the den of what appears to be some kind of hacker ship.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SLUG_BUTT_BUDDIES" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true" req="SYMBIOTE_AND_TONY" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Approach with Tony and Rig.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You hail the Slugs and put Tony and Rig on the screen. "Bet you didn't expect to see US! We've found you at last, and now it's time you finally tell us what this was all about."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Wait for a response.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slug captain looks utterly confused but soon realizes what is going on. "O-Oh. OH. OH. OHHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAH! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH! HAH! HHAAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHHAAHHAAHHAHAHAHAHAH! HAHAHAHAHAH! HAHHAHAHAH! OH. MY. GOD. You're that Rock guy, and you're that-that Leech guy! HAH! Oh my this is GOLDEN! HAHAHAH! You- you really thought this was some grand scheme? Some epic plot? HAHAHAHAH! NO! It was a pure coincidence! We do this all the tiiiime. We really go you TWICE? That is incredible! You're such a loser! HAHAHAH! Heh..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Attack them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>No one's going to miss these assholes. Hopefully this should prove to be quite cathartic.</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/> 
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Leave them.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SYMBIOTE_AND_TONY" lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Tony and Rig aren't with us. This isn't worth our time anymore.</text>
		<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It was dumb to come all the way out here for something as petty as revenge.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="BUTT_BUDDIES_REVENGE">
	<text>It seems during the fight the two main Slugs escaped on a lifepod, but you quickly scoop it up before they can get away. You bring them back on board to deliberate what to do with them. Rig and Tony both propose one simple punishment- treat them with their own medicine.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Agree.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Rig grabs one of the Slugs by the tail as Tony holds the other in place, and together they force one Slug down the gullet of the other. One screams as the other chokes, and the two roll on the floor in agony until the pain becomes unbearable and you finally put them out of their misery. You can see Tony and Rig aren't quite as satisfied with this as they had hoped, but they're glad to finally have laid them to rest.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="BUTT_BUDDIES_REWARD"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>No. This can't keep happening.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Torturing the Slugs like that will do no one any good. Instead, you grant them a quick and painless death. You can tell Tony and Rig aren't quite as satisfied, but the death of the Slugs satisfies them nonetheless.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="BUTT_BUDDIES_REWARD"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="BUTT_BUDDIES_REWARD">
	<text>Tony and Rig cannot thank you enough for your help. As a reward for finally settling this, Rig gives you a special prototype weapon blueprint under works by Zulfiqar.</text>
	<weapon name="MISSILES_ENERGY"/>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					NEMESIS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_DROPPOINT" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_START">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS_DROPPOINT"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS_DROPPOINT"/>
</ship>
<event name="DEFEAT_NEMESIS_DROPPOINT">
	<text>Moments before death, you see Leah whip out a teleporter recall button. "This isn't the last you've seen of me, Federation scum!" Leah warps away, leaving you utterly confused.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="NEMESIS_DROPPOINT" unique="true">
	<text>Looks like a Rebel ship is here, waiting for you. You can't quite make out what the ship is though at first.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_DROPPOINT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="NEMESIS_FIRST"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEMESIS_FIRST" unique="true">
    <text>The captain hails you, revealing themselves to have obnoxiously bright blue hair and a smug glare. "Didn't expect to see me here, did you? Haha, that's right, I have returned! It wasn't easy tracking you through time and space, but now I will end you once and for all!"</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS" hostile="false"/>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Uh, who are you?</text>
        <event>
            <text>The Rebel captain stutters. "H-huh? You don't remember me? It is I, your arch-nemesis, Leah, the infamous BEAM MASTER! Mwahahahah! You think you're so clever, always coming in to ruin my day. But I'm getting smarter. You won't beat me this time, beyatch!"</text>
            <ship hostile="true"/>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>계속...</text>
                <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="NEMESIS_ENCOUNTER" unique="true">
	<text>Looks like a Rebel ship is here, waiting for you. You can't quite make out what the ship is though at first.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_NEMESIS" max_group="1" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="NEMESIS_ENCOUNTER_LIST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_NEMESIS" max_group="1" lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="NEMESIS_FIRST"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="NEMESIS_ENCOUNTER_LIST">
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS"/>
	
	<event load="NEMESIS_ION"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS_LANIUS"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS_HACK"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS_ASB"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS_REPAIR"/>
	<event load="NEMESIS_SPEECH"/>
</eventList>

<textList name="NEMESIS">
	<text>At first you assume the ship here is just another standard Rigger, but reconsider when you hear the distinct yet painfully ordinary voice of that nuisance Elena. Or was it Leo? No, that's a guy's name...</text>
	<text>"Haha, I bet you thought I was dead! I never die! Get dunked on, beyatch!" Oh boy, not her again...</text>
	<text>"You know what, I'm done fighting you. This is all so pointless." Leah waits for a moment. "Haha, psych! You should have seen the look on your face! HAHA! Now I'm going to kick your ass for REAL this time! Just you wait, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"I still haven't forgotten our showdown at Prospect 17! Real smooth use of that industrial Mining Beam! You might have amputated my left index finger, but now I'm going to amputate your face! Beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"You know, those idiots in command keep telling me not to use only Beams! Absolute morons, I tell you what! Wait, what was I doing... Oh right. Die beyatch!"</text>
	<text>You wait for the ship's captain to speak, but you only pick up a hoarse cough. "S-sorry, my throat hurts from all the yelling. I have to whisper. I'm still going to get you this time, BEYATCH! Ouch, that hurt..."</text>
	<text>Right in front of you teleports Leah, just as confused as you are. "Huh? Oh, sorry, wrong ship. Just ignore this." Leah beams away back to her own ship, where she hails you again. "Die, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"Hah, remember that time when I almost killed you back in the Yura Nebula? No!? I do! I swear it happened. I was so close. Now, I'm finally going to go ALL the way this time, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"Yo, what's up! You won't believe what I've been up to! I wrote a diss track! And it's about YOU! It goes somethin' like this..." You wait, but no rapping comes. "Okay, sooo I forgot the lyrics. So let's just skip that, and get to the killing, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"BOO! Haha, scared you, didn't I?! That trick always works back at camp. I can tell because those cowards try and pretend they weren't scared, just like you're doing now! Whatever, now it's ass-kicking time, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"Guess what, I'm climbing the ranks! My commander finally stopped addressing me entirely yesterday. That just shows how much he respects me! You know, you could use a little respect, worm. I'll put the fear of god in 'ya, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"My brother Kyle's stationed in the Duskbringer Capitol right now, and he won't be quiet about those annoying explodey hologram freaks. And then I tell him about you, and that shuts him up. How does it feel to be such a pain in the ass, people hate you more than DUSKBRINGERS?! Hah, must suck to suck beyatch!"</text>
	<text>You wait for the ship to make any sort of movement, but there's nothing. Suddenly, Leah startles awake. "Uh, you didn't see me sleeping, right? Oh thank god, it would be so embarrasing if you caught me asleep at my post. Wait a minute... I should be fighting you, beyatch!"</text>
	<text>"I'm getting sick and tired of seeing you everywhere I go! It's like you're following me... creep! That's what you are, some freak obsessed with me because I'm so amazing. Well I don't think highly of stalkers, beyatch!"</text>
</textList>
<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_DEFAULT">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<textList name="DEFEAT_NEMESIS">
	<text>"Not cool dude! You can't even imagine how awkward it is to keep asking Rebel Command for more of these ships! You have no idea what it's like to keep dying over and over and having to start all over again with a new ship each time!" Leah warps away.</text>
	<text>"Ack! Not again! Trust me, this isn't the last you've heard of me, beyatch!" Leah warps away.</text>
	<text>"Noooooo! This is only my 13th most humiliating defeat! Uh, not to say I've been defeated before this." Leah warps away.</text>
	<text>"Agh, ack, wagh, bleck. Is this what dying feels like? I-I can see the light..." Leah falls to the ground, but opens her eyes again a few moments later. "Oh, I'm not dead. Alright then..." Leah warps away.</text>
	<text>Leah puts up her middle finger in a display of contempt and warps away. You aren't sure where she warps away to, but apparently they don't mind taking her back.</text>
	<text>"I prepared so many good one-liners for when I would defeat you, and now they've all gone to waste! Noooooo!" Leah warps away.</text>
	<text>"The words I have to say to you cannot be said in a PG-13 environment, but you know what I'd tell you if I could!" Leah warps away.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEFEAT_NEMESIS">
	<text load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="NEMESIS" unique="true">
	<text load="NEMESIS"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Here we go again.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_ION" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_ION">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_ION" unique="true">
	<text>"Remember when you used the reactor powering the shield generator at Delta-Base 9T-83 like an EMP field to shut off my ship? Genius move by the way - not to say you're actually smart of anything, just lucky - well it got me thinking. All this electricity stuff... it seems pretty powerful. So, screw the Beams! I'm the ION MASTER now! Get ioned, beyatch!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_ION" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Here we go again.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_MISSILES" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_MISSILES">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_MISSILES" unique="true">
	<text>"I met this weirdo named Sylvan and he was selling these Missile weapons. For some reason he marked them up stupidly high (I mean seriously, 75 scrap for a LETO?!) but I knew this was finally my chance to kick your ass! I had to sell all of my ammunition and drones to get this, but it's all worth it, beyatch!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_MISSILES" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Here we go again.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_LANIUS" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_LANIUS">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_LANIUS" unique="true">
	<text>Leah appears on the screen, eyes bulging out of their sockets. "Ack-this was a mistake. I went through the Swarmlands and found a bunch of Lanius, and thought I might be able to get them to help me - next thing I knew they dismantled my O2 system and took control of the ship! Do me a favor and kill them, then kill yourself next! Beyatch!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_LANIUS" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Here we go again.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_HACK" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_HACK">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_HACK" unique="true">
	<text>"I can still feel the burns from that time you trapped me in the medical room on Prodigy 43-A and used the system override to turn the nanobots against me! But this time, I've learned! I've brought with me all the hacking tech you could ever need! Yes, it cost me my weapons. But... uh... okay maybe this wasn't a very good idea."</text>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="shields" amount="0"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_HACK" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Here we go again.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_REPAIR" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_REPAIR">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_REPAIR" unique="true">
	<text>"This time you'll find I've prepared! I've invested heavily into a set of ADVANCED BOARDING DRONES! Mwahahahah! You're going to finally taste the taste of bitter defeat, beyatch!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_REPAIR" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Here we go again.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEMESIS_ASB" unique="true">
	<text>Leah appears on screen, attempting to make it look like she's laughing. "You're probably wondering what I'm laughing about. Well, I'll never tell..."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Fine by me.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hahah... wait what? No, I was joking. Of course I'll tell. I just didn't want to ruin the surprise... HAHA! I hacked an ASB! Get bounced, beyatch!"</text>
			<environment type="PDS" target="enemy"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>It says its targeting you.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh... shit shit shit, I've goofed hard. No matter - I'll kill you first and deal with this buggy piece of garbage later!"</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_SPIDER" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_DEFAULT">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_SPIDER" unique="true">
	<text>"Hahahah! I thought I might find you here! Thought you could run from me, your arch-nemesis? Well you thought wrong! And I have a special surprise for you... I just bought an ARMY of alien spiders that I plan to unleash upon your crew to destroy you!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_SPIDER" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Where'd you get spiders from?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, this brood guy sold them to me. Discounted too! Kind of weird the boxes were so small. But that's irrelevant... prepare to meet your end, beyatch!"</text>
			<boarders min="30" max="30" class="tinybug"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEMESIS_SPEECH" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_SPEECH">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_NEMESIS"/>
</ship>
<event name="NEMESIS_SPEECH" unique="true">
	<text>"We meet again, my arch nemesis! Mwahaha! It is I, Leah the Destroyer, the Harbinger of Chaos, Damner of the Unworthy! The powerhouse of the Rebellion, the center of its strength."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEMESIS_SPEECH" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Right...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"There is a reason for which Vance has sent me here. And yes, it was his personal request that I be the one to defeat you. Don't look further into that. Not that you could, for you won't be alive much longer. For too long the Rebellion has been stiffled by mongrels like you. No more!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uh huh.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Today is the day you die. Today, I, Leah, shall finally teach you a lesson. I shall take the throne. Mwahahahahah. MWAHAHAHAHA- wait shit. I didn't mean to press that!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>Suddenly. Leah's engines flare up and her FTL drive activates. "Nononono-this can't be happening. God damn it! I'll get you next time, beyaaaaatcccchhhh-"</text>
							<instantEscape/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Check the storage.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SYLVAN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<ship name="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" auto_blueprint="MU_TRAVELING_MERCHANT">
	<destroyed load="SYLVAN_DESTRUCTION"/>
	<deadCrew load="SYLVAN_CREWKILL"/>
</ship>

<event name="SYLVAN_CREWKILL">
	<text>이것이 실반의 마지막인 것처럼 보이지만 갑자기 텔레포터의 신호가 감지되더니... 또다시 습격했네요? 실반이 당신의 갑판에 다시 나타납니다. "낯썬이, 쩌를 업쌔는 건 그러케 쒸운 일이 아니에요!"</text>
	<boarders min="1" max="1" class="sylvan"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>그것으로 충분하지 않았는지, 더 많은 슬러그가 순간이동 해 왔습니다! 이 녀석들은 대체 어디서 온 걸까요?</text>
			<boarders min="2" max="3" class="slug"/>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_DESTRUCTION">
	<text>실반은 얼굴 전체에 난 베인 상처에서 피를 흘리며 무릎을 꿇었습니다. 그는 헐떡거리며 마지막 몇 마디를 남기고는 쓰러집니다. "낯썬이... 이것이... 가찌 있는 일이었기를 바래요..." 방랑하는 행상인은 더 이상 없습니다.</text>
	<unlockCustomShip shipReq="PLAYER_SHIP_SYLVAN" silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_SYLVAN_3</unlockCustomShip>
	<hiddenAug>MARKER_KILLED_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_DESTRUCTION_2"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_DESTRUCTION_2">
	<text>두터운 슬러그 수리 젤이 부서지기 시작하는 함선을 붙들고 있었지만, 결국 압박을 받다 함선이 터져버렸고 화물 컨테이너가 여기저기 흩어졌습니다. 당신은 먼저 잔해를 수거하여 신호 방해 장치, 일부 지도 데이터, 그리고 한번도 본 적 없는 황금색 레이저 무기를 발견했습니다.</text>
	<unlockCustomShip shipReq="PLAYER_SHIP_LIMIT_3" silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_LIMIT_4</unlockCustomShip>
	<reveal_map/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
	<weapon name="GATLING_SYLVAN"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>화물을 모은다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>첫 번째 화물 상자를 퍼 올려 안에 있는 모든 스크랩을 비웠습니다.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 더 많은 스크랩을 찾았습니다.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 무기와 더 많은 보급품을 찾았습니다!</text>
							<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 보급품들 사이에 있는 드론을 찾았습니다!</text>
									<autoReward level="HIGH">drone</autoReward>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>계속...</text>
										<event>
											<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 엄청난 양의 연료와 스크랩이 들어 있는 것을 발견했습니다.</text>
											<autoReward level="HIGH">fuel</autoReward>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>계속...</text>
												<event>
													<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 엄청난 양의 미사일과 스크랩이 들어 있는 것을 발견했습니다.</text>
													<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles</autoReward>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>계속...</text>
														<event>
															<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 엄청난 양의 드론 부품과 스크랩이 들어 있는 것을 발견했습니다.</text>
															<autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts</autoReward>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>계속...</text>
																<event>
																	<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 새로운 보조장비와 약간의 보급품이 들어 있는 것을 발견했습니다!</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>계속...</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>또 다른 화물 상자를 열어 더 많은 보급품을 찾았습니다!</text>
																			<autoReward level="HIGH">stuff</autoReward>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>계속...</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>또 다른 상자를 열어 엄청난 양의 미사일을 찾았습니다!</text>
																					<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles_only</autoReward>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>계속...</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>또 다른 상자를 열어 엄청난 양의 드론 부품을 찾았습니다!</text>
																							<autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts_only</autoReward>
																							<choice hidden="true">
																								<text>계속...</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>또 다른 상자를 열어 더 많은 스크랩을 찾았습니다.</text>
																									<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
																									<choice hidden="true">
																										<text>계속...</text>
																										<event>
																											<text>마지막 상자를 열자 당연하게도 더 많은 스크랩이 나왔습니다!</text>
																											<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
																										</event>
																									</choice>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SYLVAN_ATTACK">
	<text>어떤 미친 이유에서, 당신은 방랑하는 행상인을 공격하기로 결정했습니다. 정말로 이렇게 하시겠습니까? 행상인은 당신이 직면하게 될 가장 강력한 적일수도 있으니 그와 겨루려면 단단히 준비하는게 좋을 것입니다.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>그래!</text>
		<event>
			<text>당신은 실반에게 무기를 겨누고 전투를 준비합니다. "낯썬이... 이렇게 나오는 건가요? 쩡말 부끄럽네요... 우리가 찐구가 될 쑤 이쓸 거라고 쌩각했던게..."</text>
			<hiddenAug>MARKER_ATTACK_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
			<boarders min="3" max="3" class="snail"/>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>끔찍한 생각이다. 기각!</text>
		<event>
			<text>실반은 당신을 이상한듯이 바라보지만 아무 말도 하지 않고 당신이 다음에 할 말을 기다리고 있습니다.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>거래한다.</text>
				<event load="SYLVAN_TRADES"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>먼저 자원을 좀 판다.</text>
				<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_MENU"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>그의 제안을 거절한다.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Maybe a different time then, ssstranger! I'm ccccertain thisss won't be the lassst we sssee each other, in thisss reality or another."</text>
					<choice>
						<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 

<eventList name="SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT">
	<event load="SYLVAN_LASERS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_BEAM"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ION"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_TRASH"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ATTRIBUTES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_STATUS"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND">
	<event load="SYLVAN_LASERS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_BEAM"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ION"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_TRASH"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ATTRIBUTES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_STATUS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_RACE"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="SYLVAN_TRADES">
	<event load="SYLVAN_LASERS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_BEAM"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ION"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_TRASH"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ATTRIBUTES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_STATUS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_UTILITY"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_RACE"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_MINELAUNCHERS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_DRONES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_HEKTAR"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_LASERS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_BEAM"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ION"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_TRASH"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ATTRIBUTES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_STATUS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_UTILITY"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_RACE"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_MINELAUNCHERS"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_DRONES"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_HEKTAR"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_RARE"/>
	<event load="SYLVAN_ANCIENT"/>
</eventList>

<event name="SYLVAN">
	<preventQuest/>
	<runFromFleet closest="true"/>
	<preventBossFleet forever="true"/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_merchant" global="true" req="SYLVAN_BEACON_CHECK">
		<color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>방문하지 않은 송신소입니다.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="SYLVAN_STANDARD">
		<event name="NEUTRAL_EVENTS" req="MARKER_KILLED_SYLVAN"/>
		<event name="SYLVAN_ATTACKED" req="MARKER_ATTACK_SYLVAN"/>
		<event name="SYLVAN_BETRAYED" req="MARKER_BETRAYED_SYLVAN"/>
		
		<event name="SYLVAN_GIFT" req="DIFFICULTY_CASUAL"/>
		<event name="SYLVAN_GIFT" req="SYLVAN_DIFFICULT_NORMAL_CHECK" lvl="1" max_lvl="1"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_LASTSTAND">
	<preventQuest/>
	<runFromFleet closest="true"/>
	<preventBossFleet forever="true"/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_merchant" global="true" req="SYLVAN_BEACON_CHECK">
		<color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>방문하지 않은 송신소입니다.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="SYLVAN_STANDARD">
		<event name="NEUTRAL_EVENTS" req="MARKER_KILLED_SYLVAN"/>
		<event name="SYLVAN_ATTACKED" req="MARKER_ATTACK_SYLVAN"/>
		<event name="SYLVAN_BETRAYED" req="MARKER_BETRAYED_SYLVAN"/>
		
		<event name="SYLVAN_GIFT_LASTSTAND" req="DIFFICULTY_NORMAL"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_GIFT">
	<text>"Ssstranger ssstranger! Good to ssssee you. Have sssome ssscrap, on the house. Now that'sss out of the way, care for a trade?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_STANDARD"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_GIFT_LASTSTAND">
	<text>"Ssstranger ssstranger, this issss it, eh? Now, I'd never do thisss with anyone elssse... but I like you, ssstranger. And you have a lot of presssure on you right now. Have sssome ssscrap, on the house. Now that'sss out of the way, care for a trade?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_STANDARD"/>
	</choice>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_ATTACKED">
	<text>"Ahhh, sssstranger. How good to sssee you again. You left ssso quickly lassst time we met. Heh, and to think I thought you weren't a coward. I sssuppossse it'sss time we finisssh thissss."</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<jumpEvent>SYLVAN_RUN</jumpEvent>
	<boarders min="3" max="3" class="snail"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_BETRAYED">
	<text>As soon as Sylvan spots you, he immediately jumps away. Seems your encounter with him back at that rift still lingers in his mind...</text>
	<instantEscape/>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_RUN">
	<text>"Tssk tsssk. You aren't getting away that eassssily ssstranger! You ssstarted thisss, and we will finisssh thisss."</text>
	<damage amount="2" system="engines" effect="fire"/>
	<damage amount="3" system="engines" effect="fire"/>
	<resetFtl/>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_DROPPOINT">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_merchant" global="true" req="SYLVAN_BEACON_CHECK">
		<color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>방문하지 않은 송신소입니다.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_GIFT">
		<event name="SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT" req="DIFFICULTY_CHALLENGE"/>
		<event name="SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT" req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_GIFT">
	<text>"낯썬이, 낯썬이! 쩌어는 쩡찍한 방황하는 행쌍인 씰반이에요. 쩨가 짤 이쩌버리는 경향이 이찌만 아마 우리는 처음 만나쓸 꺼에요. 쩌는 방대한 현씰들을 여행해꼬 멀티버쓰가 제공하는 많은 것드를 보아써요. 짱사를 쫌 할 쑤 이쓸까요? 혹씨 이걸로 썰득이 된다며언 썬물도 하나 드릴 쑤 있는데에..."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true" req="sylvan">
		<text>(실반) 실반으로 실반을 맞이한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"당씬은 낯썬이는 커녕 나, 나 짜씬이네요. 그래도 할인은 안되는게 아쓉네요. 멀티버쓰에는 무한한 내가 이꼬 그들 모두에게 꽁짜 쓰크랩을 쭐 쑤는 업써요!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>그가 무엇을 제공하는지 본다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>먼저 자원을 좀 판다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_MENU"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>공격!</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_ATTACK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>그의 제안을 거절한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Maybe a different time then, ssstranger! I'm ccccertain thisss won't be the lassst we sssee each other, in thisss reality or another."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT">
	<text>"낯썬이, 낯썬이! 쩌는 쩡찍한 방황하는 행쌍인 씰반이에요오. 쩨가 짤 이쩌버리는 경향이 이찌만 아마 우리는 처음 만나쓸 꺼에요. 쩌는 방대한 현씰들을 여행해꼬 멀티버쓰가 제공하는 많은 것드를 보아써요. 짱사를 쫌 할 쑤 이쓸까요?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="sylvan">
		<text>(실반) 실반으로 실반을 맞이한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"당씬은 낯썬이는 커녕 나, 나 짜씬이네요. 그래도 할인은 안되는게 아쓉네요. 멀티버쓰에는 무한한 내가 이꼬 그들 모두에게 꽁짜 쓰크랩을 쭐 쑤는 업써요!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>그가 무엇을 제공하는지 본다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>먼저 자원을 좀 판다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_MENU"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>공격!</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_ATTACK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>그의 제안을 거절한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Maybe a different time then, ssstranger! I'm ccccertain thisss won't be the lassst we sssee each other, in thisss reality or another."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SYLVAN_STANDARD">
	<text load="TEXT_SYLVAN_GENERIC"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="sylvan" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>(실반) 실반으로 실반을 맞이한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"당씬은 낯썬이는 커녕 나, 나 짜씬이네요. 그래도 할인은 안되는게 아쓉네요. 멀티버쓰에는 무한한 내가 이꼬 그들 모두에게 꽁짜 쓰크랩을 쭐 쑤는 업써요!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC FINAL" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false">
		<text>그가 무엇을 제공하는지 본다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false">
		<text>그가 무엇을 제공하는지 본다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_TRADES"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="2" blue="false">
		<text>먼저 자원을 좀 판다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_MENU"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_SLUG_UNIQUE" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="true">
		<text>실반에게 하고 싶은 이야기가 있습니다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER_STORY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_ZOLTAN_UNIQUE" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="true">
		<text>실반에게 하고 싶은 이야기가 있습니다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_LIZARD_STORY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_MORPH" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="true">
		<text>실반에게 하고 싶은 이야기가 있습니다.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_MORPH_STORY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="4" blue="false">
		<text>공격!</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_ATTACK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="5" blue="false">
		<text>그의 제안을 거절한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"그럼 다음에 보쬬 낯썬이! 쩌는 이것이 이 현씰이나 다른 현씰에서 우리의 마지막 만남이 아닐거라고 확씬해요!"</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<textList name="TEXT_SYLVAN_GENERIC">
	<text>"Sssstranger sssstranger, ssso niccce to sssee you again. Care for some trade?"</text>
	<text>It seems the traveling merchant has found his way to this beacon. "Fancccy ssseeing you here, sssstranger! Got sssome new goodsss..."</text>
	<text>"Sssstranger ssstranger, I sssee we meet again!" The merchant sticks out his tentacle, showing off several things he's stashed in his coat.</text>
	<text>The traveling merchant waves to you as soon as you jump in. "Aaaah, ssstranger ssstranger ssstranger. Sssso good to sssee you!"</text>
	<text>"Sssstranger ssstranger, we reunite at lasssst! Got ssssome new ssstock sssinccce the lassst time we sssaw each other..."</text>
	<text>"Sssstranger ssstranger, why, I don't believe my eyesss! I kid, it'ssss no sssurprissse we've found each other again."</text>
	<text>"Sssstranger ssstranger, what a coincccidenccce we meet again! Jussst a joke, why elssse do you think I came here?"</text>
	<text>A massive and well armed Slug ship is resting here. Looks like it's the traveling merchant! "How niccce to sssee you, ssstranger! Come in, come in!"</text>
	<text>"Ssstranger, ssssometime I'll have to tell you the ssstoriessss of my travelssss. But for now, shall we do businessss?"</text>
	<text>A bright blue Slug hails you, a fat cigar in his mouth, but he perks up when he sees you. "Sssstranger! Why hello there! Have you come to trade?"</text>
	<text>"Aaaah ssstranger, I figured I might ssssee you here. It'sss a fine day for ssshopping, you got a minute to ssspare?"</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		SPECIAL QUESTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		PREIGNITER
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER_STORY">
	<text>"쫗아요 낯썬이! 혹씨... 무기 쪼기 쩜화기에 대한 이야기를 들어본 쩍이 있나요? 그건 인간-맨티쓰 쩐쨍쭝에 안티쿰 찌구의 씨민인 짹쓴 뉴맨이이 쩌음으로 만든 강력하안 보쪼장비였찌요"</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_PREIGNITER_QUEST" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"하찌만 멀티버쓰 쩐쟁이 씨작되고 얼마 지나지 않아써 이 기쑬은 너무 강려카고, 너무 부란쩡하고, 너무 찌명쩍이라느은 이유로 금찌를 당해써요. 더 이쌍 그걸 찾는건 불가능에 가까워요 쩌도 짲아 봤다는걸 믿어쭈세요"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"하찌만 들어봐요 낯썬이, 짹쓴 뉴맨은 싸실 이걸 발명해낸게 아니에요... 훔찐거쬬! 누구에게써 훔쳐쓸까요? 무려 씬비하고 아쭈 오래된 쫑족에게써쬬. 쩌는 그들에 대해 잘 모르찌만 쩐썰에 따르면 그들은 오벨리쓰크라 불리고 과거에 우쭈를 지배해때요. 흥미찐찐한 이야기찌요?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"이 오벨리쓰크들에게 무쓴 일이 쌩겼는찌는 모르겠찌만 그들의 짠재가 은하계 여기쩌기에 남아 이따는 건 알고 이찌요. 쩌는 쑬찝에서 한 남짜가 여기써 멀찌 않은 유쩍에 쩨가 차꼬 있는 쪼기 쩜화기 기쑬이 이쓸 쑤도 이따고 말하는 걸 들어써요!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"이쩨에 말해줄께요 낯썬이. 바로 쩐에 나는 그 유쩍으로 가써 내 쏜으로 그걸 얻으려고 했찌만 당씬이 나타나써요. 내 함썬을 한번만 보면 알 쑤 있겠찌만 나는 그런 우쑤운 보쪼짱비는 필요 없어요. 그러니 여기 이 좌표를 드리고 행운을 빌어 드릴께요. 이게 다예요 낯썬이이. 이쩨, 거래하씰래요?"</text>
									<quest event="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER"/>
									<hiddenAug>MARKER_PREIGNITER_QUEST</hiddenAug>
									<choice>
										<text>계속...</text>
										<event>
											<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_PREIGNITER_QUEST" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>예, 그 이야기는 이미 들었습니다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"그럼 왜 나한테 다씨 그 이야기를 들려 달라고 했나요? 유감쓰럽게도 쩐 나 짜신을 되풀이할 씨간이 업써요..."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_TREMOR" auto_blueprint="MU_PIRATE_ROCK_BATTLESHIP_PREIGNITER">
	<destroyed load="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER_WIN"/>
	<deadCrew load="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER_WIN"/>
</ship>
<event name="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
    <beaconType id="map_icon_merchantquest" global="true">
        <color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
        <unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인에게 받은 퀘스트의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
        <visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
    </beaconType>
	
	<text>당신은 실반이 준 좌표에 도착했습니다. 저 멀리 거대한 외계의 선박이 보입니다...</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_ANCIENT_WRECK"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>접근한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>가까이 다가가자, 선체를 온갖 이상한 외계인의 팔다리로 장식한 거대한 락맨 해적선이 지나갑니다. "너. 너는 실반의 친구다 내 생각에는. 그렇지 않고선 누가 나 소름끼치는 떨림에게 걸린 현상금을 찾으러 내 영역에 오겠는가? 너는 두려움에 떨지 않는가, 땅딸보?</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_TREMOR" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>딱히 두렵지 않다.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"떨림에게 도전하면 누구도 살아남지 못한다! 실반한테 떨림의 물건을 쫓는 용병에게 무슨 일이 일어나는지 보여준다!"</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>그래, 싸우지 않는 편이 낫겠어.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"좋은 선택이다 땅딸보. 다음번엔 실반한테 떨림의 물건으로부터 떨어지라고 말해줘라!"</text>
					<choice>
						<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>우리만 이걸 찾는 것은 아닐거다. 떠난다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>실반이 약속한 그 기술은 볼 수 없겠지만, 죽는것보단 낫습니다.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SYLVAN_PREIGNITER_WIN">
	<text>"으아아아! 으아아아아! 떨림 죽어간다! 떨림 죽어ㄱ 으아아아아!" 떨림과 그의 거대한 함선이 쓰러졌습니다. 당신은 그것의 잔해를 수거합니다.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>떨림은 죽었을 지 몰라도, 여기서 당신이 해야 할 일은 끝나지 않았습니다. 외계 구조물에 접근하자 그 거대한 함선의 무식한 크기가 당신 순양함의 1000배는 된다는게 분명해집니다...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<text>당신은 불꽃이 튀는 전자 장치들이 벽 밖으로 튀어 나온 우주선의 내부를 가로질렀고 때때로 좁은 공간에서는 어쩔 수 없이 선체가 긁혔습니다. 마침내 무기 관제실처럼 보이는 방을 발견했지만, 여기서부터는 직접 걸어서 나아가야만 합니다.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>당신의 선원은 벽에 연결된 거대한 큐브 형태의 동력원을 발견했는데, 이것이 조기 점화기인 것으로 추정됩니다. 그러나, 함선의 몇몇 지점에 아직 동력이 남아 있는것을 볼 때, 이걸 뽑았을 때 무언가 경보가 작동할 수도 있습니다. 고대 외계인의 보안 기술에 얼마 만큼의 믿음을 쏟고 싶나요?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>조기 점화기를 집는다.</text>
								<event>
									<text>당신의 선원은 조기 점화기를 조심스럽게 꺼냅니다. 몇초간은 아무일도 없는것 같았는데, 녹색 불빛이 깜빡이며 작은 기계음이 당신의 번역기가 이해하지 못하는 외게어를 내뿜기 시작합니다. 당신은 당신의 선원을 처리하기 위해 파견된 2대의 자동화 드론에게 쫓기며 빠르게 함선에서 빠져 나옵니다!</text>
									<augment name="WEAPON_PREIGNITE"/>
									<boarders min="2" max="2" class="atom"/>
									<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
									<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>조기 점화기는 놔두고 수거할 수 있는 다른것을 집는다.</text>
								<event>
									<text>당신의 선원들은 함정에 빠질 위험이 없는 것중 함선에 가져갈 수 있는 것이라면 뭐든지 샅샅이 뒤져 챙겼습니다. 아마도 조기 점화기는 미래에 또다른 탐험가들의 보상이 될 것입니다.</text>
									<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		LIZARDS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_LIZARD_STORY">
	<text>"쫗아요 낯썬이! 혹씨... 털이 나이꼬 눈이 한개인 나무 도마뱀에 대한 이야기를 들어본 쩍이 있나요? 멍쩡한 쏘리쩌럼 들린다는거 알찌만 모두 싸실이에요, 약속할게요. 쩨 눈으로 찍쩝 그들을 봐꺼든요!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_LIZARD_QUEST" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>실반이 웃습니다. "찐지한 애기를 하면 근쩌에 우호쩍이지만 원씨적인 쌩물들의 거쭈찌가 이써요. 하찌만 그들은 요쯤 힘든 씨기를 겪꼬 있어요. 헥타르 싼업은 아마 당씬도 들어 봐쓸 거에요. 그들이 요 몇년 쌔에 강제 노동을 씨키려고 도마뱀들을 납치하고 이써요. 당신은 실반이 "헥타르"를 언급할 때 경멸조의 강조를 하는 것에 주목합니다."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"이 쏘씩을 들어쓸 때 나는 그 일에 개입해써요. 쩨가 그들을 영원히 지킬 쑤는 없었기 때문에 쩨 친구인 아누락이라는 쫄탄 쑤도승에게 경비를 써게 해써요. 하찌만 몇쭈동안 그에게서 쏘씩을 듣지 못해써요. 걱쩡이 되찌만, 행쌍을 하다보니 일이 좀 밀려써 말이죠. 친구가 되어 짬깐 쌀펴봐 쭐 쑤 있나요, 낯썬이? 큰 도움이 될꺼에요."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>물론입니다.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"많이 감싸합니다, 낯썬이!"</text>
							<quest event="SYLVAN_LIZARDS"/>
							<hiddenAug>MARKER_LIZARD_QUEST</hiddenAug>
							<choice>
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>거절한다.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"괜짢아요 낯썬이. 감정 쌍하지 않아요오"</text>
							<choice>
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_LIZARD_QUEST" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>예, 그 이야기는 이미 들었습니다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"그럼 왜 나한테 다씨 그 이야기를 들려 달라고 했나요? 유감쓰럽게도 쩐 나 짜신을 되풀이할 씨간이 업써요..."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_LIZARD" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_HEKTAR_FIGHT">
	<destroyed load="SYLVAN_LIZARDS_WIN"/>
	<deadCrew load="SYLVAN_LIZARDS_WIN"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="hektar" prop="0.75"/>
		<crewMember type="worker" prop="0.25"/>
	</crew>
</ship>
<event name="SYLVAN_LIZARDS" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
    <beaconType id="map_icon_merchantquest" global="true">
        <color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
        <unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인에게 받은 퀘스트의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
        <visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
    </beaconType>
	
	<text>당신은 실반이 준 좌표에 도착했습니다. 당신은 멀리 떨어진 곳에서 표면부의 나무를 가로지르는 몇개의 거대한 구조물이 있는 크고 북적거리는 행성을 볼 수 있습니다. 이 도마뱀들이 정말 실반이 말한대로 첨단 기술에 반대한다면, 이는 상당히 인상적인 성과입니다.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>접근한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>행성에 착륙 하면서 당신은 시민들이 완전히 혼란에 빠져 당신의 함선조차 거의 눈치채지 못하는 것을 볼 수 있습니다. 어떻게 소통을 해야할지 몰라, 당신은 그들의 관심를 끌기 위해 큰 소리를 외쳣습니다. 그 소리가 당신의 함선을 향해 몸을 돌리는 근처의 주민들 대부분을 놀라게 합니다.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>어, 안녕하세요? 누구 아누락 본 사람 있나요?</text>
				<event>
					<text>무리의 지도자가 앞으로 나와 자신을 건트풋이라고 소개합니다. 다행히도 당신의 번역기는 그들의 언어를 쉽게 해석할 수 있는 것 같지만, 안타깝게도 당신이 들은 소식은 암울했습니다. "아누락은 살해당했고 반군이 공격했습니다. 불필요한 사상자지만 할 수 있는 것이 아무것도 없습니다. 그가 없다면 졸탄 평화 유지군와 연락할 수 없습니다. 헥타르 산업이 함대를 보내 그 악랄한 사업을 다시 시작했습니다.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>악랄한 사업이 뭐죠?</text>
						<event>
							<text>"우리는 좋은 일꾼입니다. 헥타르는 값싼 직원을 필요로 합니다. 그게 다입니다. 한때는 길드가 그들을 도왔지만 기밀이 누설되자 사악한 어윈이 회장직에서 쫓겨났습니다. 연방이 자신들이 주장하는 대로 은하게를 보호하고자 한다면, 당신은 이곳에 남아서 우리 국민을 보호할 것입니다. 우리는 그러는게 당신에게 손해를 입힌다는걸 이해하고 보상을 제공할 것입니다.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>도마뱀들을 헥타르로부터 지키기 위해 머무른다.</text>
								<event>
									<text>얼마 지나지 않아 헥타르 함선이 나타났습니다. 그들이 당신을 봤을 때, 물러서지는 않았지만 당신을 책망하는것처럼 보였습니다. "어... 당신으은 여기 이써선 안됩니다. 이 행썽은 헥타르 싼업(tm)의 쏘유입니다아. 불편을 끼쳐 쬐쏭합니다."</text>
									<ship load="SHIP_LIZARD" hostile="false"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>여기는 졸탄 섹터입니다. 당신들은 슬러그고.</text>
										<event>
											<text>"어어, 뭐 쌍관없찌. 내가 당씬에게 얼마를 찌불해야 꺼쪄 쭐 거십니까? 이이 도마뱀들은 당씬의 빌어먹으을 씨간을 할애하알 가찌가 없씁니다"</text>
											<choice>
												<text>그들의 뇌물을 받아들인다.</text>
												<event>
													<text>의심할 여지 없이, 당신은 이 도마뱀들을 헥타르 작업장에서의 삶으로 추락시켜버렸습니다. 하지만 누가 신경이나 쓰겠나요? 돈이 최고지!</text>
													<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
													<weapon name="SHOP_ITEM_HEKTAR_BASE"/>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>헥타르 함선을 공격한다.</text>
												<event>
													<text>당신은 스크랩에 매수당하는 몇몇 부패한 졸탄 정치인들과 다릅니다. 당신에게는 도덕심이 (아마도)있고 이 도마뱀들을 지키기 위해 최선을 다 할 것입니다.</text>
													<ship hostile="true"/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>계속...</text>
														<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>거절하고 떠난다.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>도마뱀들한테 개입하지 않는다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>첨단 FTL이 장착된 멀티버스 선박을 몰고 기술을 싫어하는 원시인들로 가득찬 영토를 통과하는 것은 그들의 문명에 좋은 영향을 미치지 않을 것입니다.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SYLVAN_LIZARDS_WIN">
	<text>헥타르 함선이 파괴 되었지만 더 많은 함선이 올 가능성이 높습니다. 건트풋도 같은 우려를 드러냅니다. "하나 처리했지만 더 많이 올 것입니다.우리 민족의 불가피한 완전 노예화... 우리는 어두운 시대에 살고 있습니다."</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>가능한 많은 도마뱀을 당신이 데려갈 것을 제안한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>도마뱀은 주저하는 것 같습니다. 도마뱀은 주저하는 것 같습니다. "기술은 우리 삶의 방식에 위험합니다. 기술은 전쟁과 폭력으로 이어집니다. 우리는 당신들의 죄악으로 우리 문화를 더럽히지 않아야 합니다. 당신들이 우리를 습격하고 돈을 위해 착취하는 차세대 헥타르가 아니라는 것을 어떻게 확신할 수 있겠습니까?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>맞습니다, 기술은 위험합니다. 그러니 당신은 이기는 편에 붙어야 합니다.</text>
				<event>
					<text>도마뱀은 당신을 그들의 외눈으로 바라봅니다. "당신은 헥타르나 반군만큼이나 나쁩니다! 우리는 당신과 함게하지 않겠습니다! 당신은 이 갑작스러운 저항에 충격을 받았지만 도마뱀들은 당신과 합류하기를 거부합니다. 당신은 그들을 남겨 둘 수 밖에 없습니다.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>우리는 위협이 되지 않습니다. 우리는 가장 가까운 역에서 주민들을 내려 줄 것입니다.</text>
				<event>
					<text>도마뱀들은 토론을 위해 재빨리 모여들었지만, 또다른 헥타르 함선이 그들 바로 뒤로 달려들어 이웃 전체를 나무에 곤두박질치게 만들었을 때 그들은 재빨리 종종걸음으로 당신의 함선에 탔습니다. 당신은 다가오는 헥타르 함대에 발각되지 않은 채 멀리 날아갑니다.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>난민을 기꺼이 받아들이는 졸탄 교역소를 만나기까지는 그리 오랜 시간이 걸리지 않았습니다. 여기 있는건 그들 시민의 작은 일부에 불과하지만 현재로서 종족을 유지하기에는 충분합니다. 모두가 내리고 건트풋만이 함선에 남았습니다.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>연방. 당신은 나의 동포들에게 좋은 일을 해줬습니다. 그들의 미래가... 밝지는 않을 겁니다. 하지만 헥타르 노동 수용소에서 여생을 보내는 것보다는 훨씬 낫습니다. 나는 저들과 함게 가지 않을 것입니다. 나는 지도자로서 저들을 실패시켰습니다. 대신, 현실을 구하는 일을 돕고 언젠가는 나머지 동포들을 자유롭게 하기 위해 당신을 따르겠습니다.</text>
									<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_GUNTPUT</hiddenAug>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="lizard">Guntput</crewMember>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>우리가 할 수 있는 일을 했지만, 떠나야만 합니다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>불행히도, 도마뱀들이 너무 혼란스러워서 어떠한 종류의 보상도 받을 수 없기 때문에 헥타르 함선 잔해의 스크랩만을 가지고 떠나야 합니다.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		MORPH
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_MORPH_STORY">
	<text>"쫗아요 낯썬이! 머리가 세개 달린 행썽을 먹는 뱀 괴물에 대한 이야기를 들어본 쩍 있나요? 없다고요오?! 하하 물논 없겠쬬. 쩨가 만든 이야기거든요. 아아 이번에는 해드릴 이야기가 없찌만 쩨가 꽤 멋찐걸 봐써요! 그것도 이야기로 쳐찔까요? 아마 그럴거에요 낯썬이..."</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_MORPH_QUEST" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"쩌는 당씬이 이쩨 모프에 대해 알고 이쓸 거라고 확씬해요. 아마도 당씬이 모르는 건 그들의 함썬은 쑤많은 모프들이 한밤쭝의 두 연인보다도 더 아늑하게 결합되어 구썽된다는... 뭐 씬경쓰찌 마세요오. 그나쩌나 모프 함썬들은 기존 쏄 함썬의 디짜인을 닮는 경향이 있는데에, 우연히 눈에 띄는 한 척을 보게 되어써요..."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"쑨양함! 아마 당씬은 그런 것에 익쑥하겠쬬, 낯썬이! 지금 여기 씰반에게 해금을 찾아써 온건 아니겠찌요 그렇쬬? 그 일이 쑨탄찌는 않을 거에요. 어떻게 하던 간에 당씬이 그 함썬을 멀쩡하게 복구하는 일은 쒸운 일이 아닐거에요. 이쩨 이 문쩨를 해결할 몇가찌 방법을 쌩각해 볼께요..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"첫번째이짜 가짱 뻔한 방법은 물론 모든 모프를 쭉이는 거찌요. 쭝분히 간단한 일이여야 하쬬... 모든 쫑류의 것들이 바글거리찌만 않았다면요. 싼쏘가 없다는 것도 쩡말 까다롭쬬. 두번째는 당씬이 어떤 기쩍을 발견해써 이것들과 쏘통하는 방법을 익혀써 그들이 당씬에게 함썬을 주도록 설득하는 거에요. 행운을 빌어요. 쎄번째 쩨가 개인쩍으로 가짱 쫗아하는 방법은 그들이 귀를 기울일 누군가를 데려가는 거에요. 우즈 마주라고 불리는 큰 모프가 이 찌역 쭈위에 있다고 들어써요. 쩨 쌩각에는 알파 기찌 쭈변의 어딘가일 것 같아요."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"이쩨, 이 쑨양함으로 향하는 쫘표를 드릴게요. 나는 당씬을 믿어요 낯썬이! 그나쩌나, 이쩨 이 얘기는 끝나쓰니... 거래할까요?"</text>
									<quest event="SYLVAN_MORPHUNLOCK"/>
									<hiddenAug>MARKER_MORPH_QUEST</hiddenAug>
									<choice>
										<text>계속...</text>
										<event>
											<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MARKER_MORPH_QUEST" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>예, 그 이야기는 이미 들었습니다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"그럼 왜 나한테 다씨 그 이야기를 들려 달라고 했나요? 유감쓰럽게도 쩐 나 짜신을 되풀이할 씨간이 업써요..."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_MORPH_CRUISER" auto_blueprint="MU_MORPH_CRUISER">
	<destroyed>
		<text>모프 순양함이 파괴되었습니다. 안타깝게도, 지금은 함선을 복원할 방법이 없지만 잔해를 수거할 수는 있습니다.</text>
		<hiddenAug>ACH_BOSS_MORPH</hiddenAug>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew load="MORPH_CRUISER_CREWKILL"/>
</ship>
<event name="SYLVAN_MORPHUNLOCK" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
    <beaconType id="map_icon_merchantquest" global="true">
        <color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
        <unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인에게 받은 퀘스트의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
        <visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
    </beaconType>
	
	<text>실반이 준 좌표에 도착했습니다. 근처에서 거대한 모프 함선이 발견된 걸 보면 언제나처럼 실반의 정보가 정확했던 것 같습니다.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MORPH_CRUISER" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>접근한다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>가까이 다가가자 순양함이 본능적으로 무기를 치켜듭니다.  "마쿠! 주카 잎 잎 룰!" 추정해보면, 그들은 당신이 그들을 쫓고 있는 이유에 대한 설명을 바라는 것 같습니다.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>대화를 시도한다.</text>
				<event>
					<text>당신은 무릎을 꿇고 위아래로 폴짝 뛰면서 지저귀는 소리와 불쾌한 소음을 몇마디 내뱉어 모프의 불안정한 소리를 따라했습니다. 모프의 반응을 보기 위해 다시 일어설 때까지 그들은 1인치도 움직이지 않았습니다. "엄... 푸 루...?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>"푸 루!"</text>
						<event>
							<text>"푸 루! 푸 루! 푸 루!" 모프들이 일제히 꿈틀대기 시작한 다음 원을 따라 돌면서 외쳤습니다. "푸 루! 푸 루! 푸 루!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"커르 커르 티그." 모프들은 도는걸 멈추더니 다시 함선을 관리하러 갑니다. 이 모든 것이 시간 낭비였던 것 같습니다.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>공격!</text>
										<event>
											<text>"아투 아투! 이릴 툭 툭!" 모프가 전투를 준비하고, 당신도 준비해야 합니다.</text>
											<ship hostile="true"/>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>계속...</text>
												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>내버려 둔다.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="bloblarge">
				<text>(우즈 마주) "픽 픽 열라 스푸 투!"</text>
				<event load="MORPH_CRUISER_OOJMAJOO"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>공격!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"아투 아투! 이릴 툭 툭!" 모프가 전투를 준비하고, 당신도 준비해야 합니다.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>모프 함선을 피한다.</text>
				<event>
					<text>당신은 이 싸움에 대한 준비가 되어 있지 않다고 생각합니다. 다른 상황이었다면 싸울 수도 있었겠지만, 지금은 다른 걱정거리가 있습니다.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>우리는 그들을 조우할 준비가 되지 않았다.</text>
		<event>
			<text>당신은 이 싸움을 할 준비가 되지 않았습니다. 아아, 다른 날을 기다려야겠죠.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MORPH_CRUISER_OOJMAJOO">
	<text>그들의 지도자인 우즈 마주의 목소리를 듣자 모든 모프들이 멈췄습니다. 몇번 더 횡설수설하다가, 모프들이 우주선 설게도에 대한 일부 설게도를 전송했습니다. 그건 마치... 유전코드처럼 보이지만... 당신이 궁금해 할 필요는 없겠죠.</text>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_BOSS_MORPH</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>떠나기 전에, 모프들이 당신에게 선의의 선물을 제공했습니다.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MORPH_CRUISER_CREWKILL">
	<text>The Morph cruiser has been emptied of crew. It feels... unusual, walking around in the squishy, semi-organic interior as you head to the cockpit and reprogram the ship to head back to the Federation hangar. You wonder what the Federation will think when it gets there...</text>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_BOSS_MORPH</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you leave, you stop by the cargo bay of the Morph ship. Inside you find a ton of scrap, and a strange Morph that you scoop up and bring onto the ship.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="gold"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_merchant" global="true" req="SYLVAN_BEACON_CHECK">
		<color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>방랑하는 행상인의 위치입니다.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>이미 방문한 송신소입니다. 더 이상 흥미로운건 없습니다.</visitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventFleet/>
	<preventQuest/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false" default="SYLVAN_ROYAL_NORMAL">
		<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_DEAD" req="MARKER_KILLED_SYLVAN"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_SYLVAN_NEMESIS" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_OBELISK">
	<destroyed load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_WIN"/>
	<deadCrew load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_WIN"/>
</ship>
<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_NORMAL">
	<text>Scans show that Sylvan should be here as usual, but where his ship once was is now a smoking wreck! What kind of monstrous vessel could have dethroned Sylvan?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Investigate closer...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you pull closer, a strangely familiar vessel uncloaks nearby, followed by an equally familiar voice. "Long time no see, beyatch! You thought you were rid of me, you thought you could run, you thought you could hide... but NO! I have found you! Me, YOUR ARCH NEMESIS! MWAHAHAHAH!"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_SYLVAN_NEMESIS" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We know each other?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Seriously? You don't remember me? It's ME! The one who's almost killed you hundred times before! I've been following you since the beginning of your journey! How do you NOT remember me?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Oohhhh yeah, you're Leo!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT?! That's a GUY'S name! I'm LEAH! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Er... sorry?</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Uhhhh... oh right, you're Lizzy!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT?! I'm LEAH! Lizzy is a stupid name! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Er... sorry?</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Ah, I remember. You must be Leilani!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT?! I'm LEAH! Leilani is a stupid name! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Er... sorry?</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Ah, I remember. You must be Liam!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT?! That's a GUY'S name! I'm LEAH! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Er... sorry?</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Ah, I remember. You must be Leviticus!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT?! What kind of stupid ass name is Leviticus! That's a guy's name! I'm LEAH! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Er... sorry?</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Too late to do anything.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You fly away, hoping you never have to encounter the ship responsible for this.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT">
	<text>"Oh shut up. You aren't sorry for anything. I thought we had something going. Like, one of those cool rivalries you see in movies. But all this time, you didn't give a single shit about me. Well guess what! I've learned a thing or two from our past encounters. See, the reason I could never beat you was because time after time I specialized in only one thing. But those days are over. New ship, new guns, new armor. I've already killed your little Slug friend. And now, it's time I finally put an end to this little facade of mine by killing you."</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event> 

<ship name="SHIP_SYLVAN_NEMESIS_DEAD" auto_blueprint="MU_BEAM_MASTER_OBELISK">
	<destroyed load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_WIN_DEAD"/>
	<deadCrew load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_WIN_DEAD"/>
</ship>
<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_DEAD">
	<text>Suddenly, a strangely familiar vessel uncloaks nearby, followed by an equally familiar voice. "Long time no see, beyatch! You thought you were rid of me, you thought you could run, you thought you could hide... but NO! I have found you! Me, YOUR ARCH NEMESIS! MWAHAHAHAH!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SYLVAN_NEMESIS_DEAD" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We know each other?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Seriously? You don't remember me? It's ME! The one who's almost killed you hundred times before! I've been following you since the beginning of your journey! How do you NOT remember me?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Oohhhh yeah, you're Leo!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"WHAT?! That's a GUY'S name! I'm LEAH! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Er... sorry?</text>
						<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT_DEAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uhhhh... oh right, you're Lizzy!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"WHAT?! I'm LEAH! Lizzy is a stupid name! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Er... sorry?</text>
						<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT_DEAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ah, I remember. You must be Leilani!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"WHAT?! I'm LEAH! Leilani is a stupid name! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Er... sorry?</text>
						<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT_DEAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ah, I remember. You must be Liam!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"WHAT?! That's a GUY'S name! I'm LEAH! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Er... sorry?</text>
						<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT_DEAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ah, I remember. You must be Leviticus!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"WHAT?! What kind of stupid ass name is Leviticus! That's a guy's name! I'm LEAH! I... I thought you were joking. All of this time, I keep fighting you. I follow you to the ends of the Multiverse, rematch after rematch. And despite all of that, you couldn't even bother so much as to remember my name?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Er... sorry?</text>
						<event load="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT_DEAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_FIGHT_DEAD">
	<text>"Oh shut up. You aren't sorry for anything. I thought we had something going. Like, one of those cool rivalries you see in movies. But all this time, you didn't give a single shit about me. Well guess what! I've learned a thing or two from our past encounters. See, the reason I could never beat you was because time after time I specialized in only one thing. But those days are over. New ship, new guns, new armor. Now, it's time I finally put an end to this little facade of mine by killing you."</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_WIN_DEAD">
	<text>"I... I still lost... Even with all of that... I wasn't a match for you. Well... see you in the next life, beyatch..." Leah falls to the ground, and for the first time, she doesn't beam away. Your "nemesis" is finally dead.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_ROYAL_WIN">
	<text>"I... I still lost... Even with all of that... I wasn't a match for you. Well... see you in the next life, beyatch..." Leah falls to the ground, and for the first time, she doesn't beam away. Your "nemesis" is finally dead.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Inspect the merchant's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems Sylvan is in horrible condition. Leah might have been stronger than before, but there's no way she single handedly killed him. Sylvan must have already been worn down by the fleet of Obelisk and Aces to get here. You aren't sure if you can save him.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>There's nothing we can do.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You know you can't save him, but you can at least make the merchant's final moments comfortable. "Ssstranger, thisss isss the end. I want you... to have thissss... You're the Multiverssse'ssss biggessst badassss now. Go make me proud."</text>
					<weapon name="ANCIENT_BEAM_3"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="salt">
				<text>(Obyn) "My dearest Sylvan!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You weren't wrong Obyn... we did ssssee each other again..." Sylvan puts his hand to his chest, as if feeling if he still has a pulse. His face shows a look of disappointment at what he feels. "I don't have much longer, Obyn. Do you remember that sssship we sssaid we would build together? Well... I finisssshed it. The blueprints in my cargo bay. If there'ssss one thing I can trussst about my ssship, it'sss that the cargo bay alwaysss survivesss the fight..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Thank you sssstranger, for reuniting me with Obyn one lassst time. It hassss been an honor. There'sss a little extra sssomething in that cargo bay for you." Sylvan turns to Obyn one last time. "Obyn... I love you. Goodbye." And with that, the traveling merchant slumps over unconscious. Obyn's tears mark stains on his robes, and you aren't sure if you can do anything to save him.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>There's nothing we can do. Go check the cargo bay.</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_DIES"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="medbay" lvl="3">
								<text>(최고급. Medbay) Save him.</text>
								<event>
									<text>You rush Sylvan to the Medbay to be healed. Once he's in a stable condition, he thanks you. Sylvan and Obyn have another one of their awkward distant hugs, and then Sylvan turns to you. "Well, ssstranger. Guessss we better check on that cargo, then go sssave reality, eh?"</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Go check the cargo bay.</text>
										<event load="SYLVAN_LIVES"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="clonebay" lvl="3">
								<text>(최고급. Clone Bay) Save him.</text>
								<event>
									<text>You rush to register Sylvan in your Clone Bay. Once his clone emerges from it, he thanks you. Sylvan and Obyn have another one of their awkward distant hugs, and then Sylvan turns to you. "Well, ssstranger. Guessss we better check on that cargo, then go sssave reality, eh?"</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Go check the cargo bay.</text>
										<event load="SYLVAN_LIVES"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="RECON_AND_TELEPORT">
								<text>(최고급. TP + Recon Tele) Save him.</text>
								<event>
									<text>You quickly beam back Sylvan and allow the regenerative effects of the teleporter to kick in. Sylvan and Obyn have another one of their awkward distant hugs, and then Sylvan turns to you. "Well, ssstranger. Guessss we better check on that cargo, then go sssave reality, eh?"</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Go check the cargo bay.</text>
										<event load="SYLVAN_LIVES"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="billy">
				<text>(Billy) Billy seems to want to say something.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Billy rushes over to Sylvan, shaking him, trying to lift him off the floor. "Come on brother, don't die here! Oh, how could I let ussss grow ssso apart, I'm ssssuch a fool. An assshole... Pleassse Sssylvan, don't let our sssaga end here before I had a chanccce to redeem myssself."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>Sylvan tries to sit up, but groans in pain. "Even to the lassst minute, you care more about yourssself. You drove me away from Hektar jussst ssso you could keep up your little sssslave trade with that bassstard Irwin. And look where that got both of you."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>Billy starts sobbing uncontrollably. "I know, I know. Pleasssse Sssylvan, I can't watch you die. I don't want to lossse my brother, you're the only perssson who ever wasss by my ssside."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>계속...</text>
										<event>
											<text>Sylvan puts a tentacle on Billy's suit, pulling him closer. "It'ssss far too late to apologizzze for the passst. You want to make up for your passsst? Acccept you're a sssshit person, move forward, and help the sssstranger blow thessse Rebelsss and cube freakssss to kingdom come." Sylvan slumps over, unconcious. Billy begs for you to do something - anything.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>There's nothing we can do.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You know you can't save him, but you can at least make the merchant's final moments comfortable. "Ssstranger, thisss isss the end. I want you... to have thissss... You're the Multiverssse'ssss biggessst badassss now. Go make me proud."</text>
													<weapon name="ANCIENT_BEAM_3"/>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="medbay" lvl="3">
												<text>(최고급. Medbay) Save him.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You rush Sylvan to the Medbay to be healed. Once he's in a stable condition, he thanks you. Billy and Sylvan stare at each other awkwardly for a few moments, until Sylvan finally says, "Right now, we have more important thingsss to do. Let'ssss go sssave reality, and talk about family drama later."</text>
													<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
													<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="clonebay" lvl="3">
												<text>(최고급. Clone Bay) Save him.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You rush to register Sylvan in your Clone Bay. Once his clone emerges from it, he thanks you. Billy and Sylvan stare at each other awkwardly for a few moments, until Sylvan finally says, "Right now, we have more important thingsss to do. Let'ssss go sssave reality, and talk about family drama later."</text>
													<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
													<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="RECON_AND_TELEPORT">
												<text>(최고급. TP + Recon Tele) Save him.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You quickly beam back Sylvan and allow the regenerative effects of the teleporter to kick in. Billy and Sylvan stare at each other awkwardly for a few moments, until Sylvan finally says, "Right now, we have more important thingsss to do. Let'ssss go sssave reality, and talk about family drama later."</text>
													<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
													<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="medbay" lvl="3">
				<text>(최고급. Medbay) Save him.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You rush Sylvan to the medbay to be healed. Once he's in a stable condition, he thanks you. "Way to sssshow the Rebellion we don't messss around! Ssstranger, you have done me a great ssserviccce. I shall now be at yourssss."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
					<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="clonebay" lvl="3">
				<text>(최고급. Clone Bay) Save him.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You rush to register Sylvan in your Clone Bay. Once his clone emerges from it, he thanks you. "Way to sssshow the Rebellion we don't messss around! Ssstranger, you have done me a great ssserviccce. I shall now be at yourssss."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
					<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="RECON_AND_TELEPORT">
				<text>(최고급. TP + Recon Tele) Save him.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You quickly beam back Sylvan and allow the regenerative effects of the teleporter to kick in. "Way to sssshow the Rebellion we don't messss around! Ssstranger, you have done me a great ssserviccce. I shall now be at yourssss."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="sylvan">Sylvan</crewMember>
					<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SYLVAN_DIES">
	<text>Heart broken, Obyn has little left to do than retrieve the blueprints Sylvan mentioned. True to his confidence, the cargo bay looks to be in perfect condition. On the table sits a USB drive, but what catches your eye the most is a massive golden Gatling weapon in the center of the room. On it is a tag, which reads "For you, sssstranger."</text>
	<weapon name="GATLING_SYLVAN_HONOR"/>
</event>
<event name="SYLVAN_LIVES">
	<text>Together, Obyn and Sylvan open the cargo bay doors. True to his confidence, the cargo bay looks to be in perfect condition. On the table sits a USB drive, but what catches your eye the most is a massive golden Gatling weapon in the center of the room. On it is a tag, which reads "For you, sssstranger." Sylvan shrugs and admits he's had it for quite a while. "It'sss just a thing, eh? Guessss you're the Multiverssse'ssss biggessst badassss now, ssstranger!"</text>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_CREW_SYLVAN</hiddenAug>
	<weapon name="GATLING_SYLVAN_HONOR"/>
</event>


<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		NEXUS QUEST
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_MARRIAGE_FAVOR">
	<text>Sylvan leans in closer, so Obyn can't hear you. "Now, I feel a little cheap asssking you to do thisss, but ssssinccce we ssshare a ssship now, I can't exactly leave to go get it myssself. There'sss a very ssspecccial item I want to give my dear Obyn, but unfortunately, it'ssss not eassssy to get."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go on.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"To explain, I think I'll have to tell you a ssstory. You like thossse, right? Well, I've heard the Guild issss keeping a rare statue of an equinoid carved entirely out of diamond. Issssn't that great?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Naturally when I heard of thissss, I knew I had to get it. Normally I would have ssssold it, but it'll make a great wedding gift inssstead! The Guild will be sssso furiousss, and who doesn't love pissssing them off?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"I'll give you the coordinates for this cache. Try and sssstop by it if you can, and grab it for me. I would be mossst apprecccciative ssstranger!"</text>
							<quest event="SYLVAN_CRYSTALPONY_1"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>그가 무엇을 제공하는지 본다.</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Sell some resources.</text>
								<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_MENU"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Don't need any trades today.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Maybe a different time then, ssstranger! I'm ccccertain thisss won't be the lassst we sssee each other, in thisss reality or another."</text>
									<choice>
										<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
										<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_SYLVAN_2" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_SYLVAN_ALT">
	<destroyed load="SYLVAN_2_DESTROY"/>
	<deadCrew load="SYLVAN_2_CREWKILL"/>
</ship>
<event name="SYLVAN_2_CREWKILL">
	<text>It seems as though this is the end of Sylvan, but suddenly a teleporter signal registers - you've been boarded, again? Sylvan reappears on your deck. "Friend, it'ssss not sssso eassssy to get rid of me!"</text>
	<boarders min="1" max="1" class="sylvan"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As if that wasn't enough, even more Slugs beam aboard! Where are these guys coming from?</text>
			<boarders min="2" max="3" class="slug"/>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_CRYSTALPONY_1" unique="true">
	<text>You've arrived at the coordinates Sylvan gave. A Guild cache is nearby, but it's surrounded by the wreckage of many Guild ships. It doesn't take long to spot the cultprit... and it's Sylvan?!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SYLVAN_2" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Well, I'll be. Friendo sssshmendo, if it ain't you! Ssssay, didn't think I've been seeing you here, eh?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>You aren't Sylvan.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Of coursssse I'm Sssylvan, friendo! Jussst not the one you know. We live in a Multiverssse, you know. Unfortunately, I need thisss here pony thing. Not sssure why, I jussst want it."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Not if we can help it!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Then let the battle commenssse, eh friendo?"</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Alright, you can have it.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Avoid Sylvan.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't really sure where Sylvan came from, or why his ship looks different, but something tells you this isn't right.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>함선에서 무언가를 한다.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>아무것도 하지 않는다.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SYLVAN_2_DESTROY">
	<text>This new Sylvan has been destroyed. His ship breaks apart, revealing a massive amount of scrap left from the cargo.</text>
	<weapon name="LIST_WEAPONS_LOOT_BOSS"/>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="15" max="15"/>
		<item type="scrap" min="275" max="275"/>
		<item type="missiles" min="25" max="25"/>
		<item type="drones" min="25" max="25"/>
	</item_modify>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You open the cache, and find the pony statue tucked away in a corner. However, you jump back in surprise when the creature suddenly comes to life and runs a lap around the room. You aren't sure this is what Sylvan intended - but you try and hail him anyways. He seems surprised to see the pony is a living creature too. "Huh, how peculiar. Well, I'm not ssssure that'sss quite what I need. Well, come by and visssit me again ssstranger, and I'll think of sssomething elssse. Feel free to take the pony with you if you want."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="ponyc">Crystal</crewMember>
			<quest event="SYLVAN_CRYSTALPONY_2"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_CRYSTALPONY_2">
	<text>You've returned to Sylvan, who looks fairly peeved, though you suspect not towards you in particular. "No, no. Thisss won't do... Taking care of an equinoid on thisss sship isss too risssky. I'll have to think of ssssomething elssse...</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_TRAVELING_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, that'ssss it! Sssstranger, I got a new favor to asssk of you. But thisss time, there'ssss more in it for you than jussst some sssilly payment from me. I'm talking the kind of richesss you wouldn't believe! But it comes at a massssive risssk, ssstranger."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I'm listening.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Ever heard of the Nexussss, ssstranger? Well, it'sss the cccenter of the Multiverssse they sssasy. A vassst region of ssspace easssily accessssed by any Multiversssse. Usually only realitiesss that are very sssimilar in nature can reach each other, but the Nexussss is where you might jusssst find anything!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>계속...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Naturally, ssstranger, I wanted to sssee it for myssself. I went there - only to find millions, nay, billionssss of fellow Ssssylvanss all making their way there too. It wassss an opportunity like no other! A brilliant trade hub of Sylvans of all kindssss interacting with each other!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>계속...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"I'm ssssure SSSSOMEONE there hasss what we're looking for. You'll probably be able to make a fortune too, or maybe ssssome new friendsss! Sssso what do you sssay, ssstranger ssstranger?"</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Take me to the Nexus!</text>
										<event>
											<text>"Then off you go! Bessst of luck, ssstranger! And try and bring me a crystalline pony sssstatue, would you? Or sssomething elssse of equal worth."</text>
											<choice>
												<text>계속...</text>
												<event load="WARP_TO_NEXUS"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>We have to put our primary mission first.</text>
										<event>
											<text>"Oh, of courssse, of courssse! My bad ssstranger. Well, thanksss for the help anywayssss. Here'sss a little ssssomething extra ssspecial for you."</text>
											<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We have to put our primary mission first.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, of courssse, of courssse! My bad ssstranger. Well, thanksss for the help anywayssss. Here'sss a little ssssomething extra ssspecial for you."</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="WARP_TO_NEXUS">
	<secretSector/>
</event> 

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		CONVERSIONS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_CONVERT_MENU">
	<text>"Low on sssscrap, sstranger? High on resssourcccesss? Well lucky for you ssstranger, I can take care of that!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Sell some fuel.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_FUEL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false">
		<text>Sell some ammunition.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_AMMO"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="2" blue="false">
		<text>Sell some droneparts.</text>
		<event load="SYLVAN_CONVERT_DRONES"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 

<event name="SYLVAN_CONVERT_FUEL">
	<text>"Fuel! Heh heh, can never have enough. But I'll take sssome off of your hands, if you desssire."</text>
	<!--5-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Sell 5 fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-5" max="-5"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="10" max="10"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Sell 5 fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-5" max="-5"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="7" max="7"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--10-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="1">
		<text>Sell 10 fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-10" max="-10"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="20" max="20"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="1">
		<text>Sell 10 fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-10" max="-10"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="15" max="15"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--15-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="2">
		<text>Sell 15 fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-15" max="-15"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="30" max="30"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="2">
		<text>Sell 15 fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-15" max="-15"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="22" max="22"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--nevermind-->
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_CONVERT_AMMO">
	<text>"Missiles! Crucccial for any heavy payload, but if you find yourssself with more than you can handle ssstranger, I'll gladly buy sssome off of you."</text>
	<!--5-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Sell 5 missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-5" max="-5"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="15" max="15"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Sell 5 missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-5" max="-5"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="11" max="11"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--10-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="1">
		<text>Sell 10 missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-10" max="-10"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="30" max="30"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="1">
		<text>Sell 10 missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-10" max="-10"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="22" max="22"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--15-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="2">
		<text>Sell 15 missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-15" max="-15"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="45" max="45"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="2">
		<text>Sell 15 missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-15" max="-15"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="33" max="33"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--nevermind-->
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 
<event name="SYLVAN_CONVERT_DRONES">
	<text>"Drone partsss! If you find yourssself with too many partsss and not enough usssesss for them, I think I can sssolve your problemsss..."</text>
	<!--5-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Sell 5 parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-5" max="-5"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="25" max="25"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Sell 5 parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-5" max="-5"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="20" max="20"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--10-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="1">
		<text>Sell 10 parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-10" max="-10"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="50" max="50"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="1">
		<text>Sell 10 parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-10" max="-10"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="40" max="40"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--15-->
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="2">
		<text>Sell 15 parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-15" max="-15"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="75" max="75"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="2">
		<text>Sell 15 parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Another day, another profit for both of ussss, eh ssstranger?"</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-15" max="-15"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="60" max="60"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_DROPPOINT</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="7" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES_LASTSTAND</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>SYLVAN_TRADES</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--nevermind-->
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="1" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_STANDARD</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="SEC SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="3" blue="false">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>SYLVAN_DROPPOINT_NOGIFT</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event> 

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		LASERS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_LASERS">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, any ssself ressspecting Multiversssse traveler knowssss they need sssome gear if they're going to ssssurvive."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_LASERS</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		BEAM
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_BEAM">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, any ssself ressspecting Multiversssse traveler knowssss they need sssome gear if they're going to ssssurvive."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_BEAM</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		ION
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_ION">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, any ssself ressspecting Multiversssse traveler knowssss they need sssome gear if they're going to ssssurvive."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_ION</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		MISSILES
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_MISSILES">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, any ssself ressspecting Multiversssse traveler knowssss they need sssome gear if they're going to ssssurvive."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_MISSILES</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		TRASH
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_TRASH">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, asss a Multiversssse traveler yourssself, you sssurely know jussst how ussseful garbage isss on your own ssship! Yesss, I'm ssselling you garbage. Don't be mad."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_TRASH</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		SPECIAL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_ATTRIBUTES">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, any ssself ressspecting Multiversssse traveler knowssss they need sssome gear if they're going to ssssurvive."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_ATTRIBUTE</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		STATUS EFFECTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_STATUS">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, what'sss a little warcrime to who during war, eh? I've got my tentaclesss on sssome new tech, come and look!"</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_STATUS</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		SUPPORT
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_UTILITY">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, not every weapon has to be about killing. I know you probably don't agree, but ohhhh ssstranger I've got my hand on ssssome sssupport weapons you might be interesssted in."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_UTILITY</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		RACE
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_RACE">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, wasss to a few assorted sssectorsss reccently, picked up ssssome rare weaponssss that might interessst ya'."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_RACE</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		MINELAUNCHER
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_MINELAUNCHERS">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, wasss to a few assorted sssectorsss reccently, picked up ssssome rare weaponssss that might interessst ya'."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_MINELAUNCHERS</store>
</event>


<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		HEKTAR
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_HEKTAR">
	<text>"Trussst me sssstranger, I'm not ssssponsssored by Hektar Indusssstries. Neverthelesssss, ssshady asss they are, they make some fine weaponry. I have ssssome extra gunsss and modulesss in my ssstorage, come take a look!"</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_HEKTAR</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		RARE
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_RARE">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, got sssome rare thingsss on sssale, ssstranger!"</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_RARE</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		DRONES
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_DRONES">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, I might normally sssell gunssss, but I've gathered quite the ssstock of dronesss lately. Maybe you could ussse one?"</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_DRONES</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
		ANCIENT
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="SYLVAN_ANCIENT">
	<text>"Aaaaah. Ssstranger ssstranger, found this ssspooky ruin a while ago, and inssside found tech like you or I've never sssseen! Come, take a look."</text>
	<store>STORE_SYLVAN_ANCIENT</store>
</event>


<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CALLIE THE CALCULATOR
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE"> <!--different math problems-->
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE_V1"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE_V2"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE_V3"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE_V1">
	<text>An MV portal opens nearby, and a bright green Auto-ship exits. "Well golly, I'm Callie the Calculator, and you must be [STUDENT NAME HERE]. I'm so excited to be your teacher here at [SCHOOL NAME HERE]!!! Let's begin! What's 2+3?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MATH_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>5</text>
		<event>
			<text>"OMG That's correct! G-g-g-g-good job [STUDENT NAME HERE]! Next question!!! What is 8x12?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>84</text>
				<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>1218</text>
				<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>96</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Yay!!! You're doing amazing! N-n-next question!!! [404 FATAL ERROR - QUESTION INVALID]</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>7</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE_V2">
	<text>An MV portal opens nearby, and a bright green Auto-ship exits. "Well golly, I'm Callie the Calculator, and you must be [STUDENT NAME HERE]. I'm so excited to be your teacher here at [SCHOOL NAME HERE]!!! Let's begin! What's 8-4?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MATH_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>13</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>4</text>
		<event>
			<text>"OMG That's correct! G-g-g-g-good job [STUDENT NAME HERE]! Next question!!! What is 9/3?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>3</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Yay!!! You're doing amazing! N-n-next question!!! [404 FATAL ERROR - QUESTION INVALID]</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>6</text>
				<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>43</text>
				<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>2</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE_V3">
	<text>An MV portal opens nearby, and a bright green Auto-ship exits. "Well golly, I'm Callie the Calculator, and you must be [STUDENT NAME HERE]. I'm so excited to be your teacher here at [SCHOOL NAME HERE]!!! Let's begin! What's 4*4?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MATH_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>8</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>12</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>16</text>
		<event>
			<text>"OMG That's correct! G-g-g-g-good job [STUDENT NAME HERE]! Next question!!! What is 2+2+2?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>7</text>
				<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>6</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Yay!!! You're doing amazing! N-n-next question!!! [404 FATAL ERROR - QUESTION INVALID]</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>.</text>
						<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>3</text>
				<event load="CALLIE_MAD"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_MATH_AUTO" auto_blueprint="MU_AUTO_MATH">
	<destroyed load="CALLIE_DEAD"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="CALLIE_PROBLEM" thisFight="true" clearOnJump="true" minTime="20.0" maxTime="20.0"/>
</ship>
<eventList name="CALLIE_PROBLEM">
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_1"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_2"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_3"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_4"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_5"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_6"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_7"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_8"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_9"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_10"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_11"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_12"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_13"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_14"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_15"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_16"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_17"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_18"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_19"/>
	<event load="CALLIE_PROBLEM_20"/>
</eventList>

<textList name="CALLIE_WRONG">
	<text>"Oh no! That's wrong [STUDENT NAME]... I am so disappointed. There will be consequences for this."</text>
	<text>"Oh dear. I am so s-s-s-s-sorry for your parents. Maybe my next student won't be such a disappointment!"</text>
	<text>"Oops. Oh well, there's a spot in hell for students like you!"</text>
	<text>"You're going to d-d-detention! Try not to be an idiot next time!"</text>
	<text>"Come on dearie, it's just a math problem! There's no room in the gene pool for people like you!"</text>
	<text>"Wow, I thought better of you [STUDENT NAME]! Guess we're going to have to try another way of educating you! With force!"</text>
	<text>"Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! Oops! [AUDIO FILE CORRUPTED - CONTINUING WITH REEDUCATION PROTOCOLS]"</text>
	<text>"What good will the Rebellion do with people like you? You need to learn your math better [STUDENT NAME!]"</text>
	<text>"Judging by your performance, you will never be accepted into college and thus never have a meaningful life. As your teacher, I have decided to take mercy on you and end your existence."</text>
</textList>
<event name="CALLIE_MAD">
	<text load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="CALLIE_WRONG">
	<text load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	<damage amount="3"/>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_CORRECT">
	<text>"Good job [STUDENT NAME], that's correct!"</text>
</event>

<textList name="CALLIE_DEAD">
	<text>"Bad [STUDENT NAME], bad [STUDENT NAME]! Your parents WILL hear about this!"</text>
	<text>"How rude, [STUDENT NAME]! You need to learn some m-m-m-m-manners!"</text>
	<text>"I've failed as your teacher! Maybe my replacement will be able to teach you better! Oh woe is me!"</text>
</textList>
<event name="CALLIE_DEAD">
	<text load="CALLIE_DEAD"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_SALVAGE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="CALLIE_SALVAGE">
	<event>
		<text>It seems the wreck of Callie contains a special modified weapon, which you bring aboard.</text>
		<weapon name="GIFTLIST_WEAPONS_MATH"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_1">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 6-3?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>9</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>2</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_2">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 3+4+7?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>15</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>18</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>14</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_3">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the square root of 16?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>4</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>32</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>2.51</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_4">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the value of 'n' in n+5=3?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>2</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>-3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>-2</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_5">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is (1+1+1)+(1x0)?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>4</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>0</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_6">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the value of 'p' if p+2=8*6?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>50</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>46</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>48</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_7">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 2+2?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>4</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>22</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>8</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_8">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 9+10?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>16</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>19</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>21</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Wrong, but I like your thinking [STUDENT NAME]! No penalty this time!"</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_9">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 12-7?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>19</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>5</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>8</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_10">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 7+8?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>56</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>13</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>15</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_11">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 12/3?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>4</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>6</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_12">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 6*9?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>54</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>67</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>96</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_13">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the value of 'x' in 9/3+x=22?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>17</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>25</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>19</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_14">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the absolute value of 8?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>-8</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>8</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>4</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_15">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the output of f(4)=2x+3?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>11</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>16</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>There are infinite outputs.</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_16">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 457+932?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>1267</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>1389</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>1397</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_17">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 7+7?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>13</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>18</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>14</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_18">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the absolute value of -12?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>12</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>-12</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>6</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_19">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is the value of 'y' in 4y=8+4?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>8</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>6</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CALLIE_PROBLEM_20">
	<text>For a brief moment Callie stops firing. "N-n-n-next problem! What is 14/7?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>6</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>3</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_WRONG"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>2</text>
		<event load="CALLIE_CORRECT"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MV TRAVELERS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	

<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN"/>
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL"/>
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_SIREN_UNKNOWN"/>
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_CALLIE"/>
</eventList>

<!--MV REBELS-->
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL">
	<text>It appears you aren't alone! A fellow Multiverse Traveler, this time a Rebel, has already found their way to this beacon, and is moving in on your location.</text>
	<text>You were aware the Rebels had been finding their way into this sector, but you didn't expect to see a Multiverse-drive equipped vessel defending this beacon!</text>
	<text>It appears you aren't the only ship at this beacon, nor the only ship with a Multiverse-Drive here either! A hostile Multiverse Rebel ship has spotted you and is moving in to attack.</text>
	<text>"Haha! At last we have found you. It only took 768 different realities full of chocolate pudding or shape-shifting god aliens to find you here!" A beat up Multiverse Rebel ship moves in, weapons armed and ready.</text>
	<text>A confident Rebel captain of the nearby Multiverse ship boasts about his abilities at tracking you down, and swiftly gives his crew orders to attack. You figure you should do the same.</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship at this beacon looks like it has been through a lot... and for good reason! It's a Multiverse Traveler, and it seems they've tracked you down to this beacon and are looking for a fight.</text>
	<text>The Rebels are a common sight all around the galaxy, but the ship here is no ordinary Rebel. They appear to be a Multiverse-Drive equipped vessel, and they've decided to engage you in combat!</text>
	<!--new batch! 3.11-->
	<text>"You're that Universe 0 bloke! Haha, we've got you now. You're one hard fellow to track down, but in the end, the Rebellion will always win!"</text>
	<text>A Rebel Multiverse ship approaches. "You son of a buzzard, do you know how many realities we had to suffer through until we found you? This is like, the 9th version of myself to pilot the 16th version of this ship! So quit running and just die!"</text>
	<text>You're amazed at the amounts of effort these Rebels go to tracking you down. A Rebel ship in poor condition bears down on you, determined not to let you past.</text>
	<!--new batch! 4.0-->
	<text>A mute Rebel officers fumbles, performing lazy sign language your translator slowly converts to verbal communication. "A Free Mantis ripped out my tongue. I blame you. Now I'm going to kill you."</text>
	<text>You receive a hail from an overweight Rebel. "I was an MFK Ace you know, but then I took a Bio-Beam to the knee. But if I can kill you... maybe Vance will give me another chance!" You suspect he's lying, but you don't have time to refute his claim.</text>
	<!--new batch! 4.10.3-->
	<text>The pastel blue hull of a Rebel MV Traveler glides past. As soon as they spot you, they power up their weapons and engage!</text>
	<text>A Rebel ship comes screaming into the system... Literally. The captain is shouting at the top of his lungs. Some of these Rebels are complete nuts. Look like you'll have to crack another one.</text>
	<text>"Straight out of Universe 1, and the first thing I find is a Federation Multiverse Traveler? My luck is never this good! Promotion, here I come..." Seems you'll have to prove this isn't quite the lucky encounter he's looking forward to.</text>
	<text>A Rebel captain appears on the vidscreen, chewing on a squirming bowl of young Orchids. "While tracking you down, we ran out of food. Now I'm stuck eating these gross baby things. Please, just let me kill you, so I can go find some food that doesn't cry when I bite it."</text>
	<text>A nearby Multiverse travelling Rebel ship broadcasts an automated message; "Glory to the Rebellion!" You remember the time when the Rebels cared enough to actually say it themselves. At least, you get to blow them up all the same.</text>
</textList>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_MV_REBEL"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_MULTIVERSE" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_REBEL_MULTIVERSE" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_MULTIVERSE">
	<destroyed load="DESTROYED_REBEL"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEAD_CREW_REBEL"/>
</ship>

<!--MV TRAVELERS-->
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_SPAWN">
	<text>당신은 평범해 보이는 송신소에 도착했지만 스캔 결과과 근처에 유난히 큰 슬립 터널이 열리고 있음을 보여줍니다. MV 드라이브를 가진 누군가가 근처로 도약해오고 있습니다!</text>
	<choice req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="0" max_lvl="3" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SECTORS14"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="4" max_lvl="5" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SECTORS56"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SECTOR_COUNT" lvl="6" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_SECTORS7"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" auto_blueprint="LIST_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELERS">
	<surrender  chance="0.80" min="2" max="3" load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
</ship>

<event name="DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER">
	<text load="TEXT_DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_LIST"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER">
	<text>"At least... when I'm dead... I won't have to look at your stupid face anymore..."</text>
	<text>The Multiverse ship has ceased to function, sending out a mist of blue vapor from what was their drive. You scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>"Ah shit, guess I'm dead now." The Multiverse Traveler's vessel promptly shuts down.</text>
	<text>You've sent another crew of Multiverse Travelers to the great multiverse in the sky. You hope this doesn't end up being you someday down the line instead.</text>
	<text>The Multiverse Traveler has met his untimely end. That'll teach the galaxy not to mess with the likes of you.</text>
	<text>In the end, this ship wasn't much different from you. All the same, they're the dead ones, and you aren't.</text>
	<text>The defeat of this vessel marks another victory for you and your crew. You hold a celebratory toast in hopes to more successful battles after salvaging the wreck.</text>
	<text>"Aaaaaaghghghghghgh," moans the enemy captain. He gasps for air, then falls over dead. The enemy is no more.</text>
	<text>Some day, you might earn enough of a name for yourself that these ships stop trying to mess with you. But for now, you can cross another set of pillagers off the list.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine what your kill count will be by the end of your mission, and frankly you aren't sure you want to find out. Still, there's nothing stopping you from salvaging these latest remains.</text>
</textList>
<eventList name="DEFEAT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_LIST">
	<event/>
	<event/>
	<event>
		<text>As you start to leave, you do one more once over of the wreckage and are surprised to find an item left behind that you missed!</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER">
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_SCRAP"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_SCRAP"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_FUEL"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_DRONES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_SCRAP">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">fuel</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">missiles</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER_DRONES">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">droneparts</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER">
	<text>"Ahhh crap crap crap! We surrender, stop firing for the love of Newton's Third Law!"</text>
	<text>The ship sends several images of a white flag to you. You figure that's a good sign that they wish to surrender.</text>
	<text>"Ok, we messed up. But if you kill us, well that's just not very cool man."</text>
	<text>"Look, this was a bit of a mistake. Let us go, and we promise we'll never make this mistake again. Probably."</text>
	<text>"I'm a fellow Multiverse Traveler like you! Surely you understand we only wanted scrap! It was a mistake messing with you, take this and let us live!"</text>
	<text>The ship hails you, their captain soliciting a... favor for your 'pleasure' in turn for letting them live. When you express your disinterest, they offer something of more monetary value instead.</text>
	<text>The enemy hails you, speaking a mess of untranslated garble. "Apologies, I forgot to turn my translator on again." The captain pauses. "AAAAAAAAAAAAAH DON'T KILL US DON'T KILL US!"</text>
	<text>"Do you know who I am? If you kill me, my 37 wives will be absolutely devastated! Please spare me, for their sake! But also mostly mine!"</text>
	<text>"I have traveled thousands of realities and no ship has ever fared so well against me as you. You have earned the right to not be killed by me. Please stop." The enemy captain sounds triumphant, but you can see the fear in his eyes.</text>
	<text>"God, this is worse than the time we had to fight off an infestation of parasitic bat-worms! I can't believe I'm saying this, but we surrender!"</text>
	<text>"We will not surrender! Okay that's a lie, we surrender. I really don't want to die."</text>
	<text>"Ugh, I can't believe I've been brought to my knees by such an ugly bastard like you. Will you take our surrender, so my legend doesn't have to end in such a disappointing manner?"</text>
	<text>"I'm too pretty to die! Wait, maybe I can buy this stupid idiot off with some junk... wait, is my mic on?" The ship goes silent, followed by an offer of surrender.</text>
	<text>"Great, another scar for my face. I'd like to live past today, even if it means I'm going to be the mutilated amputee that you've left me as. Can I buy your mercy perhaps?"</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER_SECTORS14">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_FIGHT"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_FIGHT"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_CHOICE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_CHOICE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_FUEL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_DRONES"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_FLEET"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER_SECTORS56">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_FIGHT"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_FIGHT"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_FIGHT"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_SCRAP"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_CREW"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER_SECTORS7">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS"/>
</eventList>

<textList name="TEXT_FIGHT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER">
	<text>"Federation, you are the next of many kills that I foresee in my future! Let us duel!"</text>
	<text>"What a disgusting ship you have there! I shall be doing the Multiverse a favor by ridding it from existence."</text>
	<text>"A fellow Multiverse Traveler? A true pleasure to meet you here, new friend! Now die."</text>
	<text>"Crap, this isn't the solid gold reality. Oh, there's a ship here. Men, get ready for battle!"</text>
	<text>"Where the hell are we? This is what we get for not using a warp-bay... wait, Federation? God damn it, we're in another one of those civil war realities. Looks like we're fighting our way out of this one!"</text>
	<text>A Multiverse ship jumps in a few seconds later, ready to pillage. There's no other option but to fight!</text>
	<text>"Bow down to me, foolish ship! This reality now belongs to us!" You doubt any ship could conquer an entire reality on their own, but regardless it's time for a fight!</text>
	<text>"Apologies stranger, it's really nothing personal that we have to kill you. Scrap's a hard commodity to come by! Well not really, but you can never have enough."</text>
	<text>"Don't even bother trying to run, Federation! Your ship is forfeit to me now! Hahahah!"</text>
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a foreboding, yet strangely colored Multiverse vessel. It looks like talking it out isn't an option, because their guns are already firing!</text>
	<text>It's a common philosophy among Multiverse Travelers that all scrap they can get their hands on belongs to them. You're guilty of this quite often as well, but now another traveler has arrived and sees you as their next target!</text>
	<text>"Hello there, friend! I have a gift for you, would you like to see it?" You reluctantly ask what it is, only to be met by them charging forward in an offensive attack!</text>
	<text>"Haha, I am but 4 parallel universes ahead of you! But I will not have won until I've defeated you in EVERY universe! Yahoo!" The ship moves in to attack.</text>
</textList>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_FIGHT">
	<text load="TEXT_FIGHT_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER">
	<text>A Multiverse Traveler approaches, demanding you give them tribute. Will you give in to their demands, or fight your way through?</text>
	<text>"Ah, what a welcome surprise to see a fellow traveler! Unfortunately, I think you have something we want..."</text>
	<text>"Stop right there, Federation vessel! We claim this beacon for our own, and you're in our territory! You'll have to give us tribute if you want to pass."</text>
	<text>A Multiverse ship threatens you nearby, and it seems you might find yourself in a fight soon unless you can satisfy them with a tribute.</text>
	<text>"Ah, I see you've already found your way to this reality. I'm sure you've found your collection of riches, and have plenty to share with us, right?" You suspect this is more than just a friendly request when their weapons swivel to face you!</text>
</textList>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_CHOICE">
	<text load="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Give them a tribute of scrap.</text>
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-15"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Give them a tribute of fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-12" max="-5"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_SCRAP">
	<text load="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Give in to their demand.</text>
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-15"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Give in to their demand.</text>
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-12" max="-5"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Give in to their demand.</text>
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-20" max="-7"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_DRONES">
	<text load="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Give in to their demand.</text>
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-15" max="-5"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_CREW">
	<text load="TEXT_DEMANDS_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's a tough choice, but it's what the enemy demands.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Unfortunately, Federation laws prevent you from cloning crew while they're still alive.</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_DEMAND_FLEET">
	<text>"You're the Federation ship that the Rebels put a bounty out for! How lucky are we to find you here! Give over your flight plans, or else things will have to get rough!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice>
		<text>Give them your flight plans. [Boosts fleet for 2 jumps]</text>
		<event>
			<modifyPursuit amount="2"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't giving these guys anything. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS">
	<text>불안하게 기다리지만 터널은 계속 커져만 갑니다.</text>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_CASUAL" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CASUAL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_NORMAL" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_NORMAL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_CHALLENGE" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CHALLENGE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="DIFFICULTY_EXTREME" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_EXTREME"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CASUAL">
	<text>You expect a massive vessel to come out, but instead it's just a standard Multiverse traveler. Still a threat, but far less than you expected.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MULTIVERSE_TRAVELER" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_NORMAL">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CLANSMAN_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGI_C_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LOSTSUN_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MANTIS_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MONK_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ROCK_C_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SEPARATIST_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SLUG_C_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_STEALTH_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ZOLTAN_C_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SHELL_C_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGINEER_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LANIUS_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_KESTREL_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FED_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ORCHID_B_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CRYSTAL_C_NORMAL"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CHALLENGE">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CLANSMAN_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGI_C_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LOSTSUN_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MANTIS_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MONK_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ROCK_C_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SEPARATIST_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SLUG_C_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_STEALTH_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ZOLTAN_C_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SHELL_C_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGINEER_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LANIUS_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_KESTREL_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FED_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ORCHID_B_CHALLENGE"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CRYSTAL_C_CHALLENGE"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_EXTREME">
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CLANSMAN_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGI_C_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LOSTSUN_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MANTIS_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MONK_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ROCK_C_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SEPARATIST_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SLUG_C_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_STEALTH_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ZOLTAN_C_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SHELL_C_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGINEER_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LANIUS_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_KESTREL_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FED_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ORCHID_B_EXTREME"/>
	<event load="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CRYSTAL_C_EXTREME"/>
</eventList>

<!--CLANSMAN B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_CLANSMAN_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_CLANSMAN_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_CLANSMAN_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_CLANSMAN_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_CLANSMAN_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_CLANSMAN_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CLANSMAN_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Guild design! This must be some rare hunting vessel, who's taken it upon themselves to travel the Multiverse for rare hunts!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_CLANSMAN_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Prepare to fight!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah, a fine hunt! Don't fret, Federation vessssel, you will make wonderful prey from my men! I hope you won't go down too easssy, I could usssse a challenge for oncccce..."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CLANSMAN_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Guild design! This must be some rare hunting vessel, who's taken it upon themselves to travel the Multiverse for rare hunts!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_CLANSMAN_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Prepare to fight!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah, a fine hunt! Don't fret, Federation vessssel, you will make wonderful prey from my men! I hope you won't go down too easssy, I could usssse a challenge for oncccce..."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CLANSMAN_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Guild design! This must be some rare hunting vessel, who's taken it upon themselves to travel the Multiverse for rare hunts!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_CLANSMAN_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Prepare to fight!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah, a fine hunt! Don't fret, Federation vessssel, you will make wonderful prey from my men! I hope you won't go down too easssy, I could usssse a challenge for oncccce..."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_CLANB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_CLAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_CLANB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_CLANB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_CLAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_CLANB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_CLANB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="NEVERMISS"/>
</event>

<!--DUSKBRINGER B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Duskbringer design! The steel exterior of the ship shines from the nearest star, but your attention is drawn to their large crew of Zoltan soldiers.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ugh, another repugnant Federation pig in our way. I carry the Duskbringer message to new realities, cleansing the evils I see in my path. You will be my next target. I suggest you prepare whatever pitiful defenses you might own, though I doubt they'll be enough against me."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Duskbringer design! The steel exterior of the ship shines from the nearest star, but your attention is drawn to their large crew of Zoltan soldiers.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ugh, another repugnant Federation pig in our way. I carry the Duskbringer message to new realities, cleansing the evils I see in my path. You will be my next target. I suggest you prepare whatever pitiful defenses you might own, though I doubt they'll be enough against me."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Duskbringer design! The steel exterior of the ship shines from the nearest star, but your attention is drawn to their large crew of Zoltan soldiers.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_DUSKBRINGER_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ugh, another repugnant Federation pig in our way. I carry the Duskbringer message to new realities, cleansing the evils I see in my path. You will be my next target. I suggest you prepare whatever pitiful defenses you might own, though I doubt they'll be enough against me."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_DUSK</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_DUSK</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_DUSKB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="SHOTGUN_STEEL"/>
</event>

<!--ENGI C-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGI_C_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ENGI_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGI_C_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ENGI_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGI_C_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ENGI_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGI_C_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Engi design! The ship appears to be made of of various parts from different styles of Engi ships, an odd amalgam unlike anything you've seen.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGI_C_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I can sense... a presence. Federation-Federation! The agitation in my nanites... it [drives] me to kill. The lust for blood is-is-is overwhelming. Apoligiz-ing, death must come."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGI_C_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Engi design! The ship appears to be made of of various parts from different styles of Engi ships, an odd amalgam unlike anything you've seen.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGI_C_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I can sense... a presence. Federation-Federation! The agitation in my nanites... it [drives] me to kill. The lust for blood is-is-is overwhelming. Apoligiz-ing, death must come."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGI_C_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Engi design! The ship appears to be made of of various parts from different styles of Engi ships, an odd amalgam unlike anything you've seen.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGI_C_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I can sense... a presence. Federation-Federation! The agitation in my nanites... it [drives] me to kill. The lust for blood is-is-is overwhelming. Apoligiz-ing, death must come."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ENGI</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique drone model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ENGI</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ENGIC_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special drone amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a drone like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<drone name="DEFENSE_TRINITY_MISSILE"/>
</event>

<!--FREEMANTIS B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Free Mantis design! It appears to be stealth oriented, but still capable of both a strong offense and teleportation!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Your heads will be mine! For the glory of the Kurkataka clan!" It seems these Free Mantis aren't quite as friendly as most...</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Free Mantis design! It appears to be stealth oriented, but still capable of both a strong offense and teleportation!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Your heads will be mine! For the glory of the Kurkataka clan!" It seems these Free Mantis aren't quite as friendly as most...</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Free Mantis design! It appears to be stealth oriented, but still capable of both a strong offense and teleportation!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_FREEMANTIS_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Your heads will be mine! For the glory of the Kurkataka clan!" It seems these Free Mantis aren't quite as friendly as most...</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_FREEMAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_FREEMAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_FREEMANTISB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="UNSPOOLER"/>
</event>

<!--LOSTSUN B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_LOSTSUN_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_LOSTSUN_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_LOSTSUN_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_LOSTSUN_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_LOSTSUN_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_LOSTSUN_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LOSTSUN_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Lost Sun design! The ship seems to be armored with a thick layer of ice, and it wields an impressive arsenal of Frost weapons!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_LOSTSUN_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Lost Sun captain grunts. "Hmmph. Wasn't expecting to see a Federation vessel so far out... Well, considering that whole 'Found Moons' gig didn't work out, guess I'll have to resort to plan B and be a bounty hunter. Unlucky for you, the bounty on your ship is quite high."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LOSTSUN_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Lost Sun design! The ship seems to be armored with a thick layer of ice, and it wields an impressive arsenal of Frost weapons!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_LOSTSUN_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Lost Sun captain grunts. "Hmmph. Wasn't expecting to see a Federation vessel so far out... Well, considering that whole 'Found Moons' gig didn't work out, guess I'll have to resort to plan B and be a bounty hunter. Unlucky for you, the bounty on your ship is quite high."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LOSTSUN_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Lost Sun design! The ship seems to be armored with a thick layer of ice, and it wields an impressive arsenal of Frost weapons!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_LOSTSUN_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Lost Sun captain grunts. "Hmmph. Wasn't expecting to see a Federation vessel so far out... Well, considering that whole 'Found Moons' gig didn't work out, guess I'll have to resort to plan B and be a bounty hunter. Unlucky for you, the bounty on your ship is quite high."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_LS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_LS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_LOSTSUNB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="FROST_CHARGEGUN"/>
</event>

<!--MANTIS B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_MANTIS_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_MANTIS_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_MANTIS_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_MANTIS_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_MANTIS_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_MANTIS_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MANTIS_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Mantis design! The ship sports a massive array of bombs, but little ability to damage your hull outside of a simple beam drone.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_MANTIS_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hahahah! Explosions, death, violent shaking of metal ships as warheads detonate in starry night sky! I bring pride to Hive by igniting fiery inferno aboard this Federation ship!" These Mantis are certifiably insane, but you have little option but to fight.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MANTIS_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Mantis design! The ship sports a massive array of bombs, but little ability to damage your hull outside of a simple beam drone.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_MANTIS_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hahahah! Explosions, death, violent shaking of metal ships as warheads detonate in starry night sky! I bring pride to Hive by igniting fiery inferno aboard this Federation ship!" These Mantis are certifiably insane, but you have little option but to fight.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MANTIS_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Mantis design! The ship sports a massive array of bombs, but little ability to damage your hull outside of a simple beam drone.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_MANTIS_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hahahah! Explosions, death, violent shaking of metal ships as warheads detonate in starry night sky! I bring pride to Hive by igniting fiery inferno aboard this Federation ship!" These Mantis are certifiably insane, but you have little option but to fight.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_MANTIS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_MANTIS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_MANTISB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="BOMB_CONSERVRECYCLER"/>
</event>

<!--MONK B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_MONK_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_MONK_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_MONK_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_MONK_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_MONK_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_MONK_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MONK_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Monk design! It's uncharacteristic of Zoltan Monk ships to be so well armed, though it seems most of their weaponry is Ion related!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_MONK_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Though my oath of nonviolence myself might be a burden upon my pirate lifestyle, I hope you'll understand I'm only doing what I must to survive in this harsh multiverse. Though I may not kill you, my men can."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MONK_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Monk design! It's uncharacteristic of Zoltan Monk ships to be so well armed, though it seems most of their weaponry is Ion related!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_MONK_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Though my oath of nonviolence myself might be a burden upon my pirate lifestyle, I hope you'll understand I'm only doing what I must to survive in this harsh multiverse. Though I may not kill you, my men can."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_MONK_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Monk design! It's uncharacteristic of Zoltan Monk ships to be so well armed, though it seems most of their weaponry is Ion related!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_MONK_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Though my oath of nonviolence myself might be a burden upon my pirate lifestyle, I hope you'll understand I'm only doing what I must to survive in this harsh multiverse. Though I may not kill you, my men can."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_MONKB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_MONK</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_MONKB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_MONKB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_MONK</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_MONKB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_MONKB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="ION_CHAIN_CHARGEGUN"/>
</event>

<!--ROCK C-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ROCK_C_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ROCK_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ROCK_C_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ROCK_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ROCK_C_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ROCK_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ROCK_C_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Rock design! The tough obsidian hull of the cruiser looks as though it could take quite a beating, and you suspect they might have especially well protected primary systems.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ROCK_C_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Frightened are you, soft skinned one? I think you shall find your weapons will do little against my tech!" The ship moves in to attack. While they might be right about your weapons, you suspect boarding or even fire might be enough to damage their tech.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ROCK_C_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Rock design! The tough obsidian hull of the cruiser looks as though it could take quite a beating, and you suspect they might have especially well protected primary systems.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ROCK_C_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Frightened are you, soft skinned one? I think you shall find your weapons will do little against my tech!" The ship moves in to attack. While they might be right about your weapons, you suspect boarding or even fire might be enough to damage their tech.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ROCK_C_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Rock design! The tough obsidian hull of the cruiser looks as though it could take quite a beating, and you suspect they might have especially well protected primary systems.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ROCK_C_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Frightened are you, soft skinned one? I think you shall find your weapons will do little against my tech!" The ship moves in to attack. While they might be right about your weapons, you suspect boarding or even fire might be enough to damage their tech.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ROCK</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ROCK</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ROCKC_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="MISSILES_OBSIDIAN"/>
</event>

<!--SEPARATIST B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SEPARATIST_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SEPARATIST_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SEPARATIST_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SEPARATIST_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SEPARATIST_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SEPARATIST_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SEPARATIST_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Separatist design! The ship appears to be split in two halves, and resembles some sort of old Earth symbolism...</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SEPARATIST_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"There are [two] sides to every man. The -white-, and the -black-. The duality of man. The depth of a person's character. I'm sure it all [means] something. However, I am an AI construct, and my -left- arm has just stopped functioning. I would like to kill you quickly, before the rest of my [body] shuts down as well."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SEPARATIST_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Separatist design! The ship appears to be split in two halves, and resembles some sort of old Earth symbolism...</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SEPARATIST_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"There are [two] sides to every man. The -white-, and the -black-. The duality of man. The depth of a person's character. I'm sure it all [means] something. However, I am an AI construct, and my -left- arm has just stopped functioning. I would like to kill you quickly, before the rest of my [body] shuts down as well."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SEPARATIST_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Separatist design! The ship appears to be split in two halves, and resembles some sort of old Earth symbolism...</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SEPARATIST_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"There are [two] sides to every man. The -white-, and the -black-. The duality of man. The depth of a person's character. I'm sure it all [means] something. However, I am an AI construct, and my -left- arm has just stopped functioning. I would like to kill you quickly, before the rest of my [body] shuts down as well."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_SEPARATIST</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique drone model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_SEPARATIST</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_SEPARATISTB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special drone amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a drone like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<drone name="YINYANG_BATTLE"/>
</event>

<!--SLUG C-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SLUG_C_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SLUG_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SLUG_C_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SLUG_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SLUG_C_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SLUG_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SLUG_C_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Slug design! The bright hull of the cruiser draws your attention, though the arsenal its pointing straight at you is quite distracting as well.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SLUG_C_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Slug captain appears on screen, wearing a large hat and humming. "Had not cleared leather 'fore a... Oh, well howdy there partner. Didn't seem to see you there. That's a mighty fine ship you got. Shame I gotta rough it up a little but the bounty on your head is high as noon!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SLUG_C_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Slug design! The bright hull of the cruiser draws your attention, though the arsenal its pointing straight at you is quite distracting as well.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SLUG_C_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Slug captain appears on screen, wearing a large hat and humming. "Had not cleared leather 'fore a... Oh, well howdy there partner. Didn't seem to see you there. That's a mighty fine ship you got. Shame I gotta rough it up a little but the bounty on your head is high as noon!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SLUG_C_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Slug design! The bright hull of the cruiser draws your attention, though the arsenal its pointing straight at you is quite distracting as well.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SLUG_C_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Slug captain appears on screen, wearing a large hat and humming. "Had not cleared leather 'fore a... Oh, well howdy there partner. Didn't seem to see you there. That's a mighty fine ship you got. Shame I gotta rough it up a little but the bounty on your head is high as noon!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_SLUG</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_SLUG</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_SLUGC_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="BIG_ION"/>
</event>

<!--STEALTH B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_STEALTH_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_STEALTH_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_STEALTH_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_STEALTH_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_STEALTH_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_STEALTH_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_STEALTH_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Stealth design! The ship seems to bear camouflage similar to ones you've seen used on terrestrial planets, but seems rather inefficient in space.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_STEALTH_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the ship says nothing, your database recognizes it as a prototype the Federation was working on. Seeing it so far out here, it must be run by pirates now. No other options but to kill them and hope something good is left.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_STEALTH_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Stealth design! The ship seems to bear camouflage similar to ones you've seen used on terrestrial planets, but seems rather inefficient in space.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_STEALTH_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the ship says nothing, your database recognizes it as a prototype the Federation was working on. Seeing it so far out here, it must be run by pirates now. No other options but to kill them and hope something good is left.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_STEALTH_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Stealth design! The ship seems to bear camouflage similar to ones you've seen used on terrestrial planets, but seems rather inefficient in space.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_STEALTH_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the ship says nothing, your database recognizes it as a prototype the Federation was working on. Seeing it so far out here, it must be run by pirates now. No other options but to kill them and hope something good is left.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_STEALTH</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_STEALTH</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_STEALTHB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="BEAM_ADAPT_3"/>
</event>

<!--ZOLTAN C-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ZOLTAN_C_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ZOLTAN_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ZOLTAN_C_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ZOLTAN_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ZOLTAN_C_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ZOLTAN_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ZOLTAN_C_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Zoltan design! The ship glows with energy, and it's safe to say the Zoltan crew aboard have kept their reactor well supplied.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ZOLTAN_C_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Federation vessel, this is CFB-31. Your head is currently wanted by several inter-dimensional governments. However, this is not why we have come here. We have found you in violation of protocol-S14-W, which states clearly that military vessels exceeding the maximum hull vibrancy allocated for this system are to be destroyed. I'm sorry, but this is the law."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ZOLTAN_C_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Zoltan design! The ship glows with energy, and it's safe to say the Zoltan crew aboard have kept their reactor well supplied.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ZOLTAN_C_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Federation vessel, this is CFB-31. Your head is currently wanted by several inter-dimensional governments. However, this is not why we have come here. We have found you in violation of protocol-S14-W, which states clearly that military vessels exceeding the maximum hull vibrancy allocated for this system are to be destroyed. I'm sorry, but this is the law."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ZOLTAN_C_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Zoltan design! The ship glows with energy, and it's safe to say the Zoltan crew aboard have kept their reactor well supplied.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ZOLTAN_C_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Federation vessel, this is CFB-31. Your head is currently wanted by several inter-dimensional governments. However, this is not why we have come here. We have found you in violation of protocol-S14-W, which states clearly that military vessels exceeding the maximum hull vibrancy allocated for this system are to be destroyed. I'm sorry, but this is the law."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ZOLTAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ZOLTAN</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ZOTLANC_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="BEAM_BATTERY"/>
</event>

<!--SHELL C-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SHELL_C_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SHELL_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SHELL_C_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SHELL_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_SHELL_C_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_SHELL_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SHELL_C_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Shell design! A bright light shines through the cracks on the ship, pulsing the colors of the rainbow.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SHELL_C_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Unfortunately, ever since I injected the DNA of a hallucinogenic melon plant into my bloodstream, I have begun to see visions of the future. So far, not a single one has come true. Nevertheless, in one of them I vividly remember a ship like yours killing me. Well not exactly, but it was close enough. I'm afraid I'm going to have to kill you instead to prevent this fate."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SHELL_C_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Shell design! A bright light shines through the cracks on the ship, pulsing the colors of the rainbow.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SHELL_C_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Unfortunately, ever since I injected the DNA of a hallucinogenic melon plant into my bloodstream, I have begun to see visions of the future. So far, not a single one has come true. Nevertheless, in one of them I vividly remember a ship like yours killing me. Well not exactly, but it was close enough. I'm afraid I'm going to have to kill you instead to prevent this fate."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_SHELL_C_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Shell design! A bright light shines through the cracks on the ship, pulsing the colors of the rainbow.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_SHELL_C_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Unfortunately, ever since I injected the DNA of a hallucinogenic melon plant into my bloodstream, I have begun to see visions of the future. So far, not a single one has come true. Nevertheless, in one of them I vividly remember a ship like yours killing me. Well not exactly, but it was close enough. I'm afraid I'm going to have to kill you instead to prevent this fate."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_SHELL</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_SHELL</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_SHELLC_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="SHELL_LAUNCHER"/>
</event>

<!--ENGINEER B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGINEER_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ENGINEER_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGINEER_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ENGINEER_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGINEER_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ENGINEER_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGINEER_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Rebel Engineer design! It looks like a medical vessel, though it's armed just as well as any standard Rebel military ship.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGINEER_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hmmm, vhat do vwe have 'ere? Oooooh, zah Federation vessel? Zis should be fun! Please, die quickly, I z'am tired of holding zis stupid accent."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGINEER_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Rebel Engineer design! It looks like a medical vessel, though it's armed just as well as any standard Rebel military ship.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGINEER_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hmmm, vhat do vwe have 'ere? Oooooh, zah Federation vessel? Zis should be fun! Please, die quickly, I z'am tired of holding zis stupid accent."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ENGINEER_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Rebel Engineer design! It looks like a medical vessel, though it's armed just as well as any standard Rebel military ship.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ENGINEER_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hmmm, vhat do vwe have 'ere? Oooooh, zah Federation vessel? Zis should be fun! Please, die quickly, I z'am tired of holding zis stupid accent."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ENGINEER</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique drone model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ENGINEER</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ENGINEERB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special drone amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a drone like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<drone name="SURGEON_BATTLE"/>
</event>

<!--LANIUS B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_LANIUS_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_LANIUS_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_LANIUS_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_LANIUS_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_LANIUS_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_LANIUS_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LANIUS_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Lanius design! The ship glitters in the light of the nearby star, as its scarlet hull and sharp spikes lurch towards you.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_LANIUS_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"The swarm, food needing from boat of yours! Imminent death, becoming of you! Are going cry, infant man?" You're pretty sure that's supposed to be an insult, though your translator is struggling. Guess you'll have to prove you aren't an 'infant man.'</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LANIUS_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Lanius design! The ship glitters in the light of the nearby star, as its scarlet hull and sharp spikes lurch towards you.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_LANIUS_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"The swarm, food needing from boat of yours! Imminent death, becoming of you! Are going cry, infant man?" You're pretty sure that's supposed to be an insult, though your translator is struggling. Guess you'll have to prove you aren't an 'infant man.'</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_LANIUS_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Lanius design! The ship glitters in the light of the nearby star, as its scarlet hull and sharp spikes lurch towards you.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_LANIUS_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"The swarm, food needing from boat of yours! Imminent death, becoming of you! Are going cry, infant man?" You're pretty sure that's supposed to be an insult, though your translator is struggling. Guess you'll have to prove you aren't an 'infant man.'</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_LANIUS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_LANIUS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_LANIUSB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="SHOTGUN_TOGGLE_FIRE"/>
</event>

<!--KESTREL B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_KESTREL_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_KESTREL_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_KESTREL_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_KESTREL_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_KESTREL_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_KESTREL_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_KESTREL_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of an older Kestrel model! The fresh white coat suggests it has been outfitted with a more up to date arsenal recently.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_KESTREL_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Do you read us captain? This is Egret 5, heading from Universe 17 to provide support for this Universe's Federation. Are you familiar with the location of Node 17 in this reality?" You explain to the ship that you're also part of the Multiverse fleet. "Wait, you mean you're ALSO trying to stop the Rebellion here? No fair, that's OUR job! There can only be one savior of this galaxy, and that's going to be me! Piss off!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_KESTREL_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of an older Kestrel model! The fresh white coat suggests it has been outfitted with a more up to date arsenal recently.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_KESTREL_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Do you read us captain? This is Egret 5, heading from Universe 17 to provide support for this Universe's Federation. Are you familiar with the location of Node 17 in this reality?" You explain to the ship that you're also part of the Multiverse fleet. "Wait, you mean you're ALSO trying to stop the Rebellion here? No fair, that's OUR job! There can only be one savior of this galaxy, and that's going to be me! Piss off!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_KESTREL_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of an older Kestrel model! The fresh white coat suggests it has been outfitted with a more up to date arsenal recently.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_KESTREL_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Do you read us captain? This is Egret 5, heading from Universe 17 to provide support for this Universe's Federation. Are you familiar with the location of Node 17 in this reality?" You explain to the ship that you're also part of the Multiverse fleet. "Wait, you mean you're ALSO trying to stop the Rebellion here? No fair, that's OUR job! There can only be one savior of this galaxy, and that's going to be me! Piss off!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_KESTREL</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_KESTREL</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_KESTRELB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="LASER_LIGHT_CHARGEGUN"/>
</event>

<!--FEDERATION B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_FED_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_FED_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_FED_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_FED_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_FED_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_FED_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FED_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Federation design! However, judging from the rusting hull and crude pirate paint, it's safe to assume the Federation is no longer the owner of this vessel.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_FED_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Stop right where you are! We are the Mine Launcher police, we enforce the supreme authority of Mine Launchers in this galaxy! We're supposed to beat up people who badmouth Mine Launchers, but I realized pretty quickly there's not really a good way to keep track of that. So uh, we kind of just beat people up randomly now and pretend they were saying bad things. Like you, you filthy Mine Launcher hating scum stain. (Please just play along)."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FED_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Federation design! However, judging from the rusting hull and crude pirate paint, it's safe to assume the Federation is no longer the owner of this vessel.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_FED_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Stop right where you are! We are the Mine Launcher police, we enforce the supreme authority of Mine Launchers in this galaxy! We're supposed to beat up people who badmouth Mine Launchers, but I realized pretty quickly there's not really a good way to keep track of that. So uh, we kind of just beat people up randomly now and pretend they were saying bad things. Like you, you filthy Mine Launcher hating scum stain. (Please just play along)."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_FED_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Federation design! However, judging from the rusting hull and crude pirate paint, it's safe to assume the Federation is no longer the owner of this vessel.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_FED_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Stop right where you are! We are the Mine Launcher police, we enforce the supreme authority of Mine Launchers in this galaxy! We're supposed to beat up people who badmouth Mine Launchers, but I realized pretty quickly there's not really a good way to keep track of that. So uh, we kind of just beat people up randomly now and pretend they were saying bad things. Like you, you filthy Mine Launcher hating scum stain. (Please just play along)."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_FEDB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_FED</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_FEDB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_FEDB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_FED</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_FEDB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_FEDB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="MINELAUNCHER_GIANT"/>
</event>

<!--ORCHID B-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ORCHID_B_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ORCHID_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ORCHID_B_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ORCHID_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_ORCHID_B_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_ORCHID_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ORCHID_B_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Orchid design! The ship here seems to bear an unusual resemblance to an Earth fruit known as the "strawberry", though that's probably a coincidence.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ORCHID_B_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I don't know if you're aware, but we're kind of a big-dill here, and I don't meant to be corny, but if you don't make like a tree and leaf it's gonna be beet-down-thyme. Lettuce hope you have some aloe vera for those wounds after we... uh... crap I'm out of puns. Men, attack!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ORCHID_B_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Orchid design! The ship here seems to bear an unusual resemblance to an Earth fruit known as the "strawberry", though that's probably a coincidence.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ORCHID_B_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I don't know if you're aware, but we're kind of a big-dill here, and I don't meant to be corny, but if you don't make like a tree and leaf it's gonna be beet-down-thyme. Lettuce hope you have some aloe vera for those wounds after we... uh... crap I'm out of puns. Men, attack!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_ORCHID_B_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Orchid design! The ship here seems to bear an unusual resemblance to an Earth fruit known as the "strawberry", though that's probably a coincidence.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_ORCHID_B_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I don't know if you're aware, but we're kind of a big-dill here, and I don't meant to be corny, but if you don't make like a tree and leaf it's gonna be beet-down-thyme. Lettuce hope you have some aloe vera for those wounds after we... uh... crap I'm out of puns. Men, attack!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ORCHID</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_ORCHID</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_ORCHIDB_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="STRAWBERRY"/>
</event>

<!--CRYSTAL C-->
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_CRYSTAL_C_NORMAL" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_CRYSTAL_NORMAL">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_CRYSTAL_C_CHALLENGE" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_CRYSTAL_CHALLENGE">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<ship name="SHIP_MTBOSS_CRYSTAL_C_EXTREME" auto_blueprint="MT_BOSS_CRYSTAL_EXTREME">
	<destroyed load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DEADCREW"/>
</ship>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CRYSTAL_C_NORMAL">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Crystal design! If your days as a Multiverse Traveler have told you anything, the orange hull of this ship suggests their crew probably have some affixation with fire.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_CRYSTAL_C_NORMAL" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yo yo yo, what is UP my bros! This is DJ fyre on the beat, yo! You wanna know somethin cool, dog? Yo mama so dense, her crystal skin is already bordering on coal! Yo mama so dumb she wears herself on her wedding ring! Yo mama is so fat, she is anahedral! Alright alright, one last one. Yo mama so dumb she thought diamonds were made of silicone oxide!" The Crystal pauses while the crew in the background cheer with load harmonious shouts of "OOOOOOOOH." "Yo yo yo, was that a sick burn or what? Aight dog, enough foolin. We gonna steal your shit now."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay tribute in scrap to avoid the fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CRYSTAL_C_CHALLENGE">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Crystal design! If your days as a Multiverse Traveler have told you anything, the orange hull of this ship suggests their crew probably have some affixation with fire.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_CRYSTAL_C_CHALLENGE" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yo yo yo, what is UP my bros! This is DJ fyre on the beat, yo! You wanna know somethin cool, dog? Yo mama so dense, her crystal skin is already bordering on coal! Yo mama so dumb she wears herself on her wedding ring! Yo mama is so fat, she is anahedral! Alright alright, one last one. Yo mama so dumb she thought diamonds were made of silicone oxide!" The Crystal pauses while the crew in the background cheer with load harmonious shouts of "OOOOOOOOH." "Yo yo yo, was that a sick burn or what? Aight dog, enough foolin. We gonna steal your shit now."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Draw straws and send over a crew as tribute.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, the MV ship accepts the tribute in turn for letting you live.</text>
			<removeCrew>
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text>Tempting as it is, cloning living crew is against Federation law. God damn Federation laws...</text>
			</removeCrew>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MV_TRAVELER_BOSS_CRYSTAL_C_EXTREME">
	<text>From out of the tunnel comes a massive cruiser vessel, of Crystal design! If your days as a Multiverse Traveler have told you anything, the orange hull of this ship suggests their crew probably have some affixation with fire.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MTBOSS_CRYSTAL_C_EXTREME" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yo yo yo, what is UP my bros! This is DJ fyre on the beat, yo! You wanna know somethin cool, dog? Yo mama so dense, her crystal skin is already bordering on coal! Yo mama so dumb she wears herself on her wedding ring! Yo mama is so fat, she is anahedral! Alright alright, one last one. Yo mama so dumb she thought diamonds were made of silicone oxide!" The Crystal pauses while the crew in the background cheer with load harmonious shouts of "OOOOOOOOH." "Yo yo yo, was that a sick burn or what? Aight dog, enough foolin. We gonna steal your shit now."</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>계속...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DESTROYED">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_CRYSTAL</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DROP_CHANCE"/>
	</choice>
</event> 
<eventList name="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DROP_CHANCE">
	<event>
		<text>You find the remains of a unique weapon model amongst the ruins of the ship, but it appears it did not survive the fight. You'll have to be more careful next time, or get lucky. Fortunately, there's still a bit more supplies to take with you.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DROP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DEADCREW">
	<text>The mighty vessel has been eliminated! Within its wreckage remains plenty of scrap and supplies for the taking.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<hiddenAug>ACH_MV_CRYSTAL</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>계속...</text>
		<event load="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DROP"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="MTBOSS_CRYSTALC_DROP">
	<text>You're also surprised to find a special weapon amongst the wreckage! You've never seen a weapon like this before, so you assume it's a custom model made by the travelers themselves.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<weapon name="CRYSTAL_BURST_FIRE"/>
</event>
</FTL>